We have a multiple vehicle，multiple injury accident.
那里发生一宗连环车祸
An absolute mess from Vine Street to the valley.
劝大家走别的路
If you're in it，expect a long commute.
建议刚好正在前往的路上朋友换一条路线
If you're not，seek alternate routes.
我们迟些再谈 现在我要工作
If Dan doesn't want to do a daily rate，we can talk about a weekly rate.
如果丹不想按月薪来的话 那就算周薪吧
But I'm not goin'below a million.
但低于一百万我可不干
Let me think about it。I'm risking my reputation
让我想一想 如果我接受这个角色的话
as the host of this country's number-one
就等于是让我这个全国首屈一指的
nationally syndicated talk show to do a cameo in some cheap slasher flick.
脱口秀节目主持人去拍一部廉价的恐怖电影
Why can't these guys write me a fuckin' decent part？
他们就不能给我一个好一点的角色？
I lived through the fuckin' thing.
我受够了这倒霉事
By the way，you talk to Cathy about that Navy SEAL script？
还有 你和凯蒂谈过那海豹特种部队的剧本了吗？
Hang on a sec.
等一下
Hello？Hello？
你好？你好？
Who's this？Who's this？
是谁？你是谁？
Who are you calling？You know what？I'm sorry。I have the wrong number.
你找谁？你知道吗？很抱歉 我打错了
That's okay。Wait a minute。I know your voice.
没关系 等等 你的声音很熟悉
You sound a lot like that guy on TV。Um… Cotton Weary.
你的声音像电视上那个 嗯… 卡顿·威瑞
I do，huh？Yeah。I think he's got a really sexy voice.
是吗？是的 我认为他的声音很性感
Well，thank you.
是吗 谢谢
Wait a minute。You are Cotton，aren't you？
等等 你就是卡顿 对吗？
Oh，my God。I am talking to Cotton Weary。I can't believe this.
哦 天啊我正在和卡顿·威瑞说话 真难以置信
You got me。I've got someone on the other line.
你真有意思 我手头还有个电话
Can you hold on one second？I'll be right back，I promise.
你能等等吗 我很快就好 我保证
Yeah。Okay.
当然 好的
Andrea，I gotta call you back。Someone's on the other line.
安德鲁 我稍后打给你 有人找我
So！You a big 100% Cotton fan？
好了！你是百分百的卡顿粉丝？
Yeah！One hundred and ten percent。That's very good.
是的！百分之一百一十 太好了
So，why don't you tell me who you are？
那么 为什么不告诉我你是谁？
Ooh！You're a naughty boy。What would your girlfriend say？
哦！你真顽皮 你的女朋友会怎么想呢？
What makes you think I have a girlfriend？I know you do.
你怎么会认为我有女朋友？我知道你有
I'm right outside her bathroom door。Who is this？
我正在她的浴室外面 你是谁？
She's in the shower。She's got a nice little voice.
她正在洗澡 嗓音很甜美
Let's come in for a closer look.
不知道她的样子怎么样
She's very pretty，Cotton.
她很漂亮 卡顿
A step up from Maureen Prescott.
比莫琳·普莱斯柯特漂亮多了
Speaking of which，let's play a little game.
讲着话时 让我们来玩个游戏吧
Answer right，your girlfriend lives.
答对了 你女朋友就能活下来
Answer wrong，she dies.
答错了 她就要死
Where's Maureen's daughter，Sidney？
莫琳的女儿西德妮在哪？
Who the fuck is this？
你他妈的是哪个东西？
Somebody who'd kill to know where Sidney Prescott is！
一个死也要知道西德妮·普莱斯柯特在哪的人！
One chance，Cotton！You've got connections。Where is she？
机会只有一次 卡顿！你现在得到了 她在哪？
You listen，you fuckin' psycho。You lay a finger on Christine，
听着 你个该死的神经病你敢碰克里斯汀娜一下
and I swear I'll kill you！
我发誓我会杀了你！
Wrong answer！
回答错误！
No！Wait！Hello？Shit！
不！等等！喂？该死！
Hey！Get outta the way！
嘿！快滚开！
You just hit me！Move！
你差点撞上我！滚开！
Christine，if you're there，pick up the phone！
克里斯汀娜 在的话快接电话啊！
Christine，pick up the phone！Oh shit！
克里斯汀娜 接电话啊！哦 该死！
You have reached 911。Due to the volume of calls…
你好这里是911 由于当前来电过多…
Someone pick up the goddamn phone！Move outta the way！
该死的 快来个人接电话啊！滚开！
Shit！
该死！
Cotton，is that you？
卡顿 是你吗？
Cotton？
卡顿？
Honey？
亲爱的？
Okay，Cotton.
好了 卡顿
You know I don't like your Stab games.
你知道我不喜欢你的杀戮游戏
Who is it？Who's there？
谁？谁在那？
Christine？Hon，you all right？
克里斯汀娜？亲爱的 你没事吧？
I'm home。Jesus！You scared the shit outta me.
我回来了 老天！你把我吓坏了
You'll never believe what Just happened to me.
你肯定不会相信今天我遇上什么事了
What are you talking about？
你在说什么？
Get the hell out of here！Okay，I'm sorry，babe.
滚出去！好了 对不起 宝贝
I didn't mean to scare you that bad。It's me。Come on，open the door.
我不是有意要把你吓成那样的 是我 好了 开门吧
What are you doing？What the fuck are you doing？What？
你在干什么？你他妈的在干什么？什么？
I was just trying to take the game to the next level.
我只是在玩一下升级版的游戏
I'm sorry。Come on，open the door，Chris。The game？
对不起 好了 开门吧 克里斯 游戏？
Yeah，the game！What are you talking about？
是的 游戏而已！你在说什么？
Talking about how much fun it's gonna be to rip your insides out！
我想说的是把你的内脏给撕出来是多有意思的事啊！
Now，open the fuckin'door，Christine！
快点 打开这该死的门 克里斯汀娜！
Oh，my God！
哦 天啊！
Now you're fuckin'history，baby！
现在 我会让你变成历史 宝贝！
Christine？
克里斯汀娜？
Hon？
亲爱的？
The recent epidemic of road rage in Los Angeles.
洛杉矶交通情况最新报道
Innocent commuters，mercilessly terrorized，Chris？
无辜的驾驶员们既愤怒又不安 克里斯？
even killed by these madmen of the freeway。Don't mess around，okay？
就快被这高速路上的状况搞疯了 别玩了 好吗？
We're gonna make them confront their victims facetoface，mano a mano，
我们要让他们面对他们的受害者 来个面对面
right here on 100% Cotton.
就在百分百卡顿的节目上
Carnage on our streets。And remember，it could happen to you.
高速路上的惨剧 记住这也可能会发生在你身上
Tomorrow on 100% Cotton！Road rage.
明天的百分百卡顿！道路狂飙现象
L.A。drivers fight back.
洛杉矶驾驶员们的反击
The news is next on channel six with
接下来六号频道将播出的是
our exclusive entertainment report live…
我们独家带来的现场报道…
from tonight's celebrity premiere in Hollywood，
一部电影的好莱坞首映仪式
followed by…
接下来是…
Oh，shit.
哦 该死
Chris？
克里斯？
Is that you，babe？
是你吗 宝贝？
Chris，if you're in there，open the door。Okay，honey？
克里斯 如果你在里面就快开门 好吗 宝贝？
Chris？Come on，baby。Open the door.
克里斯？快 宝贝 来开门
Chris，whoa，whoa，whoa。Jesus！
克里斯 哇 哇 哇 天啊！
It's me，Chris。What are you doin'？Stay back.
是我 克里斯 你要干吗？离我远点儿
Stay back.
离我远点儿
Chris，what's goin' on，babe？You've gone crazy。That's what！
克里斯 出什么事了 宝贝？你疯了！
Chris，was somebody in the house？No！Get back！
克里斯 屋子里还有别人吗？没有！退后！
Okay，okay，okay。Just calm down，okay？
好 好 好 冷静一点 好吗？
Why do you want to kill me？What are you talking about？
你为什么想杀我？你在说什么呢？
Why do you wanna kill me？
你为什么想杀我？
Gimme the club。All right？Gimme the club.
把球棍给我 好吗？把球棍给我
Gimme the club，please.
求求你 把球棍给我
Oh！Christine，get outta the way！
哦！克里斯 快闪开！
Behind you！
小心后面！
Shit！
该死！
It was a simple game，Cotton。You should've told me where Sidney was.
这个游戏很简单 只要你告诉我西德妮在哪
Now，you lose.
现在 你输了
《惊声尖叫3》
Come on.
过来
Come on，Cherokee。Come on.
过来 切罗基 这边
Come on.
过来
Come on，Cherokee.
过来 切罗基
California Women's Crisis Counseling.
加州女性生活危机辅导
Hey。It's Laura from Monterey reporting to work。Can you patch me in？
嘿 我是蒙特瑞的罗拉 能帮我接入吗？
Sure。Thanks，Laura。Thank you.
当然 谢谢 罗拉 谢谢
California Women's Crisis Counseling.
加州女性生活危机辅导
How can I help you？
有什么能帮你的吗？
Hi。Do I have to say my name？
嗨 我能不说自己的名字吗？
No，you don't have to say anything you don't want to say.
可以 你不想说的可以不说
How can I help？
有什么能帮你的吗？
I'm 18 years old。And I have a boyfriend.
我今年18岁 有一个男朋友
Sometimes he hits me.
他经常会殴打我
It's okay。You can talk to me，all right？Thanks.
没事的 你可以和我说 好吗？谢谢
So，in closing，as future journalists of America，
那么 在演讲的最后 最为美国未来的媒体人
there is one thing you need to remember.
有一件事你们必须要记住
Being the best means being willing to do what the others would not.
吃得苦中苦 方为人上人
Break the rules。Stop at nothing.
打破陈规 无所畏惧
Be willing to have the world hate you，
承受住整个社会的怨气
because that is the only way you'll get the story，
只有这样你们才能得到出有价值的新闻
the facts and the fame.
报道和声誉
Thank you.
谢谢
Excuse me。Excuse me。Yes？
抱歉 抱歉 什么事？
So you're saying that we should be ready to
那么你的意思就是我们应该准备好
go out and cut each other's throats…
走向社会与他人进行冷酷的竞争…
because that's what you did.
因为你就是这么做的
Metaphorically，yes.
隐晦的来说 是的
Well，tell me，Miss Weathers，was it worth it？
请你告诉我 韦瑟斯女士这么做有多大的意义呢？
I'm so sorry。We're out of time.
抱歉 我们的时间到了
Gale Weathers，anchorwoman for Total Entertainment.
盖尔·韦瑟斯 百分百娱乐的新闻女主播
Thank you very much！
感谢你带来的演说！
There is a young man outside who wants to see you.
外面有个年轻人想见你
He says he's with the police。The police？
他说他是警察 警察？
Detective Mark Kincaid，L.A.P.D。Hello.
我是洛杉矶警方的马克·金凯德警长 你好
That's an impressive resume.
这是一个令人印象深刻的简历
Thank you。I assume you're not here for an autograph.
谢谢 不过我想你不是来这儿要签名的
I'm here because Cotton Weary's been murdered.
我来这儿是因为卡顿·威瑞的谋杀案
Someone killed Cotton？
卡顿被人杀了？
And his girlfriend.
一起遇难的还有他的女友
Someone who left something he wanted us to see.
凶手故意给我们留下了一些信息
I'll show you this because you're the Woodsboro authority，
我给你看是因为你是伍兹伯勒时间的当事人
and because you knew him.
而且你也认识这个人
But I promise you，
但是我要告诉你
if you share this with the world，it's you I'll be arresting.
如果你把这个信息泄漏出去 你将会被捕
I swear on my Pulitzer Prize，which I plan to win one day，Detective.
我以即将赢得普利策新闻奖的职业操守发誓 警长
This was left on Cotton Weary's body.
这是在卡顿·威瑞尸体边发现的
Have any idea who the girl might be？Oh，my God.
你认识这个女孩吗？哦 天啊
This is Maureen Prescott.
这是莫琳·普莱斯柯特
This is Sidney Prescott's mother.
西德妮·普莱斯柯特的妈妈
Hollywood is reeling today from news
好莱坞被一名
of the murder of controversial talk show host Cotton Weary.
饱受争议的脱口秀节目主持人卡顿·威瑞的死震惊了
Weary had only recently finished shooting a cameo as himself in the film
威瑞刚刚完成了一部自己参与拍摄的一部名叫
Stab 3，return to Woodsboro，
杀戮3 影片回到伍兹伯勒
the third and final part of the famous horror series…
这是这个著名的恐怖系列的第3部也是最后一部
based on the Woodsboro and Windsor College murders.
电影根据伍兹伯勒和温莎大学的凶杀案改编而来
Before his rise to television fame，Cotton had been imprisoned，
在他进入电视界之前 卡顿曾经被捕
and was later exonerated for
但随后就被解除了谋杀
the murder of Maureen Prescott，his former love…
他的前女友莫琳·普莱斯柯特的罪名…
Just yesterday，
就在昨天
Cotton Weary was shooting here at Sunrise Studios，
卡顿·威瑞还在升阳电影公司这里拍摄电影
his first cameo in a feature film，Stab 3.
他的影视荧幕首秀 杀戮3
Security here is tight，
目前这里现场保护森严
but we'll see if we can get a statement。Excuse me.
看看我们是否能套到一些消息 抱歉
Always a controversial man…
一个饱受争议的公众人物…
Channel Eight news。We gotta get in.
第8频道新闻节目我们得进去
No press beyond this point.
谁都不能进去
Look，you're worried about the movie，then protect the movie.
听着 你担心这部影片 那就做好保卫工作
Hire more security。Hire the National Guard。Just don't kill the movie.
多请些保安 请些国民警卫队 不要让这部影片流产
Violence in cinema is a big deal right now，Roman.
电影拍摄过程中出现凶杀案是件大事 罗曼
This is not the kind of news this studio is after.
这可不是这部影片想见到的宣传效应
So，if we stop making scary movies，
那么 如果我们不做恐怖电影
what，all the psychos will retire？Come on.
怎么 那些变态杀手就不会出现了？得了吧
I've been makin' horror movies for 30 years，
我做了30年的恐怖电影
and never had a psycho problem.
从没遇到过变态杀手这种事
He was your goddamn idea guys.
这是你找来的该死的演员
An excon with a trashy talk show？
一个结了婚的脱口秀主持人？
He must've pissed people off everyday.
他肯定每天都得罪很多人
Detectives，there's no reason to presume Cotton's death…
警长 卡顿的死…
had anything to do with this movie，is there？
和这部电影没什么关系 对吗？
He was making a movie called Stab。He was stabbed.
他接拍了一部电影叫杀戮 结果他就被杀了
Probably some psycho fan pissed off they killed Randy in Stab 2.
也许有些精神病影迷因为杀戮2里面兰迪的死而恼火
Tyson，that'd make you next，wouldn't it？
泰森 那你就会是下一个目标 不是吗？
I am not a Randy substitute。I'm my own character.
我可不是兰迪第二 我有自己的特点
Named Ricky，who works at the video store。It's an homage.
名叫瑞奇 在音像店工作 这是个荣耀
Hey！What if the killer's Sidney Prescott？
嘿！如果凶手是西德妮·普莱斯柯特呢？
I mean，what the hell ever happened to her？
我是想说 她到底有着怎样的遭遇？
She's probably in the woods livin' like the fuckin' Unabomber，man.
她可能就像大学炸弹客一样生活在森林里 伙计
I'm starting to see why Tori Spelling
我开始明白为什么托莉·史培林
and David Schwimmer didn't want to come back.
和大卫·修蒙为什么不愿回来了
Guys，this was about Cotton。We are not in any danger.
伙计们 这只是针对卡顿的 我们没有危险
「We are not in any danger，」 says Candy，page 15.
「我们没有危险」 卡迪说的 剧本第15页
I don't see you leavin'.
我可没见你打算离开
Ha！You think serious black actors my age
嘿！你觉得我这个年龄的黑人演员
can just throw away jobs？
能就这样丢掉工作吗？
It's all a business now.
现在这是笔生意
They got Usher doing Pinter offBroadway.
他们召我这样的演员去非主流的戏剧院做迎宾员
L.L。CoolJ's Shakespearin' in the park.
LL CoolJ乐队像莎士比亚一样在公园卖艺
Yeah！
是的！
Maybe it's not meant to be。Not meant to be？
也许这不该发生 不该发生？
You win that talent search for the new Sidney.
你是寻找新任西德妮选秀的冠军
50，000 girls and they pick you.
你从5万个女孩中被挑选出来
You gotta be praying this movie keeps going.
你应该祈祷这部影片不要流产
Of course I am，but not at the expense of people's lives.
当然我是该这么想 但是我不想有任何人牺牲
Oh。Cue the violins，right？
哦 可爱的小提琴 对吗？
Oh.
哦
Jesus.
天啊
Deja voodoo.
德嘉的咒语
We need this area cleared，please。Clear it.
我们要这一块清场拜托 清场了
Gale Weathers！Oh，my God！Shit.
盖尔·韦瑟斯！哦 天啊！该死！
Listen，I know we've never met，
看呐 我知道我们从没见过
and I don't mind you never returning my calls，but I have to tell you，
我也不介意你从没回过我的电话 但我必须要告诉你
after two films，I feel like I am in your mind.
在两部电影之后 我觉得你对我应该有印象
That would explain my constant headaches.
这应该就能解释我最近为什么老是头疼了
You know，I'm sorry things didn't work out on 60 Minutes II.
你知道 我对60分钟II这个节目的事感到很抱歉
But Total Entertainment，that's a pretty good fallback.
但是对百分百娱乐来说 那是一个很好的后备计划
Thank you.
谢谢
I'm sorry things didn't work out with Brad Pitt，
我很抱歉和布拉德·皮特合作的计划黄了
but being single，that's a good fallback.
但是单飞也是个不错的后备计划
Gives me more time for my work.
给了我更多的时间处理公务
After all，Gale Weathers，you're such a complex character.
说到底 盖尔·韦瑟斯 你是一个性格复杂的人
Oh，and to be played by an actress with such depth and range.
哦 现在却被这样一位心胸广阔的人来扮演
Uh，Jennifer，Nick said you wanted to…
嗯 珍妮弗 尼基说你想…
Gale.
盖尔
Dewey.
杜威
Well，surprise，surprise.
呃 惊喜啊惊喜
Someone dies and Gale comes running.
有人死了但是盖尔却开始活跃起来
Gale，I think you'll really appreciate my character work in this one.
盖尔 我想你会对我个性化的表演而感到欣慰的
Someone's helped me understand the real you。Someone？
某人正帮助我去认识一个真正的你 某人？
Your ruthless ambition，your private selfloathing，
你的无情野心 你的自怨自艾
and that lost and lonely little girl inside.
还有那内在的迷茫孤独的女儿心
Lost and lonely what？
有什么可迷茫孤独的？
You heard me。Thanks，Dewey，I'll return it.
你已经听清楚了 谢谢 杜威 稍后还给你
Lost and lonely what？
有什么可迷茫孤独的？
Little girl inside.
小女人的心思
I thought you were supposed to be in Woodsboro.
我以为你该在伍兹伯勒
Well，I'm surprised you thought about me at all.
好了 我很吃惊你还会想到我
I gotta get back to work。I really don't have time for this.
我得回去工作了 没时间应酬你
Wait a minute。You work here？Yeah.
等等 你在这儿工作？是的
The movie needed a technical advisor.
电影需要一名技术顾问
Someone who went through the real experience，knew the real people.
有人想经历真实的场景 了解真实的当事人
Hey，Dewey。Hey。Tom.
嘿 杜威 嘿 汤姆
Hey！It's the real Gale Weathers。Real from top to bottom.
嘿！这真是盖尔·韦瑟斯本人 如假包换
Tom Prinze。Watch your show all the time.
汤姆·普林斯 经常看你的节目
You're so right。Pop culture is the politics of the 21st century.
你说得对 二十一世纪的流行文化是政治
Thank you.
谢谢
And that story that you did last month on me crashing my car？
上个月的车祸事故报道也是你做的吗？
Wow，was that ever powerful journalism。Right，um，yeah.
哇哦 那是件大事 对 是的
I especially liked the way you implied that
我特别欣赏的就是你隐隐揭露了事故
it was caused by drinking and drugs.
是由酗酒和嗑药引起的
And that the tire blowout was faked。That was great.
还有那个车胎爆裂是造假的 真是大快人心
Tom，sometimes in journalism you have to…
汤姆 有时候新闻报道你必须…
Are you parked in the lot？
你的车停在停车场吗？
I should check to make sure nobody's messed with your brake line.
我得去检查一下确保没人把你的刹车线给剪断了
Who's he supposed to be？
他干什么的？
He's playing you？Him？
他扮演你？就他？
What？
怎么了？
I did not come here to fight with you，Dewey.
我不是来和你吵架的 杜威
Cotton's killer left a picture.
杀死卡顿的凶手留下一张照片
Of Sid's mom。The detectives told me.
是西德妮妈妈的 警长告诉我的
Does Sidney know about it？
死的你知道吗？
Listen，Sidney doesn't need you
听着 西德妮不想你
and your camera in her life.
和你的长枪短炮去打扰她的生活
Do you see a camera？
你哪只眼睛看到摄像机了？
Right.
好吧
You bought me this purse，didn't you？Yeah.
你给我买了这个钱包 是不是？是的
It's a habit。I walk outta the house，I turn it on and…
这是个习惯 我步行离开家时 我打开它时…
What the hell is this？Gale Weathers？
这怎么回事？盖尔·韦瑟斯？
Could I be more popular？No press.
我能更加受欢迎点吗？没有新闻
Mo press on set。Get that woman outta here.
这儿没什么新闻 把那女人给我拖出去
Yes。Mr。Milton。Let's go。Wait a minute.
是的 米尔顿先生 走 等等
Where is Detective Kincaid？I am working with Kincaid，Dewey.
金凯德警长在哪？我和金凯德在合作 杜威
Rules are rules，Gale.
没有规矩 不成方圆 盖尔
But，really，it was great seeing you.
但是 说实话 见到你很高兴
Stab 3 is a closed set.
杀戮3是这个系列的最后一部
But just up ahead is the old Seinfeld stage.
但是前面将要看到的就是古老的辛菲尔德舞台
Now，does any body need a potty break？
现在 有人想要上厕所吗？
Oh，I do。Yeah，me too.
哦 我要 是的 我也要去
Okay，let go！Thanks for your help，boys.
好了 我自己走！谢谢你们 弟兄们
Holy shit，Silent Bob.
该死 沉默的鲍勃
It's that TV news chick，Conniefuckin' Chung！
那是最近挺红的新闻女主播 该死的康妮钟
Hey，Connie，how's Maury？
嘿 康妮 莫瑞怎么样？
Dude，I think she likes me。See how she's lookin' at me？
伙计 我觉得她喜欢我 你发觉她看我的眼神了吗？
It's happening again.
事情又发生了
Cotton had a lot of enemies，Sid.
卡顿树敌不少 西德妮
The police aren't saying it's related to us.
警方也没说这事和我们有关
Do you ever think about her？
你还在想她？
Your mom？
你母亲？
None of this would've ever happened if she hadn't…
如果她当初没有… 这些事就都不会发生
If she hadn't…
如果她没有…
Why'd she have so many secrets，Dad？
为什么她有这么多秘密 爸爸？
Listen，maybe it's time you came home.
听着 也许你是时候回来了
I'm worried about you，kid.
我很担心你 孩子
Out here by yourself。You never see anyone.
独自一人在外 从不和任何人接触
The only people you talk to don't even know your real name.
唯一能和你说话的人甚至都不知道你的真名
It's as if you don't exist.
这就好像你根本不存在于这世上
That's the idea。Psychos can't kill what they can't find.
这样才好 变态杀手根本杀不了他们找不到的人
Sid，come here.
西德妮 过来
Mother needs to talk to you.
妈妈想和你说话
Everything you touch，Sid，dies！
西德妮 所有你触碰过的东西 都将凋零！
You're poison。You're just like me.
你是毒药 就和我一样
You're Just like me.
你和我一样
Oh，my God！What have they done to me？
哦 天啊！他们对我做了什么？
They'll do it to you。They'll do it to you，baby.
他们会对你下手的 他们会对你下手的 宝贝
Mom？
妈妈？
Roman？
罗曼？
Stab 3.
杀戮3
Jesus，I gotta get a new agent.
天啊我得找个新经理人
Roman？
罗曼？
Someone here？
有人在吗？
Stan，my man.
斯坦 我朋友
He does good work，huh？Thank you。Thank you very much.
他干的不错 不是吗？谢谢 非常感谢
Fuck you very much。Tyson，go to hell.
靠你妈的 泰森 去死吧
Excuse us，Sarah。Makeup tests.
抱歉 莎拉 我们在化妆测试
Yeah，makeup。You can use it。Have you seen Roman？
是的 化妆 你正合适这样 你见过罗曼吗？
Everyone in the office has gone home already。He said it was important.
办公室所有人都下班回家了 他说这很重要
Everything's important to Roman.
对罗曼来说什么事都很重要
Oh，shit！
哦 该死！
Fuck.
该死
Director's office。Sarah，it's Roman.
总监室 莎拉 是罗曼
I'm sorry I'm running late.
抱歉 我恐怕要迟到一小会儿
I'm still on the 405。I'm about ten minutes away.
我还在405 大概10分钟后到
Oh，it's no problem。I'm just lookin' at your music video awards.
哦 没关系 我只是在看你的唱片大奖的奖杯
Since I got you on the phone，let's talk about your character，okay？
既然和你联系上了 我们来谈谈你的角色 好吗？
What character？I'm Candy，the chick who gets killed second.
什么角色？我饰演卡迪 第二个被杀的小人物
I'm only in two scenes.
我就在两个场景里过过场
You're not happy with your part.
你似乎对自己的安排感到不满
I'm not happy that
我不满意的是35岁的我
I am 35 playing a 21yearold.
要去扮演一个21岁的小青年
I'm not happy that I have to die naked.
我不满意我要全身赤裸的死去
And I'm not happy that my character
还有我不满意的是我饰演的角色
is too stupid to have a gun in the house…
在她的男友被砍成鱼饼之后…
after her boyfriend's been cut into fish sticks。Mmhmm，mmhmm.
愚蠢的在家里放了把枪 是的 是的
Great，okay。So let's run the lines.
很好 好了 我们来谈具体的台词
Fine.
好吧
Page 28。Candy's big moment.
28页 卡迪的重要时刻
Page 28.
28页
Ringring。Hello？
叮铃铃 你好？
Hello？Who's this？
你好？哪位？
Who's this？This is Candy.
你是哪位？我是卡迪
Hang on。Let me get some clothes.
稍等 我穿件衣服
See？I don't understand why I have to start the scene in the shower.
看见了？我不明白我为什么要从浴室的场景开拍
The whole shower thing's been done。Vertigo。Hello？
澡都洗完了 晕了吗 喂？
And I mean，my boyfriend just died。Why am I showering？
我的意思是 我的男朋友刚刚死去 我洗什么澡啊？
Why don't we Just read the scene？
我们为什么不投入到场景中去呢？
Candy。Nice name.
卡迪 很不错的名字
Is that like Candy Cane or Candy Apple？
是不是像蔗糖或是涂了太妃糖苹果？
Whatever.
随便
Come on，who is this？
得了 你是谁？
I think you have the wrong number.
我想你打错电话了
But you know my favorite name？I'm hanging up right now.
但你知道我最喜欢的名字？我挂电话了
It's Sarah.
是莎拉
Roman，that's not the line.
罗曼 台词不是这样的
It is in my script.
我的剧本里有
Has there been another goddamn rewrite？
有哪个该死编剧把剧本重写了？
How are the fuck we supposed to learn our lines when there's a new script every 15 minutes？
每15分钟就出一个新版的剧本我们还对个屁台词啊？
It's not just a new script。It's a new movie.
这不是一个新的剧本 这是一部新的电影
What？What movie？
什么？什么电影？
My movie.
我的电影
And it's called Sarah Gets Skewered Like a Fuckin' Pig！Shit.
名字就叫莎拉像头死猪一样被串烧！该死
Still in character… Sarah？
继续扮演… 莎拉？
Shit.
该死
Thank you for calling Sunrise Picture Studios.
欢迎致电升阳电影公司
If you'd like today's commissary menu，press one.
如果你想要今天的节目单 请按一
Mr。Bridger？
布雷吉先生？
If you'd like to hear previews of upcoming Sunrise Pictures' releases，press four.
如果你想知道预告片或剧照放出的日期 请按四
If you'd like information about merchandise，press five。Come on，come on.
如果想获取影视周边产品的信息 请按五 快 快
If you're trying to reach Lot Security or you have an emergency，press six.
如果想联系警卫或者有什么紧急情况 请按六
Shit！
该死！
Oh！Fuck！
哦！该死！
Look，I wanna get something straight.
听着 我把话挑明了吧
I only got into this because the police asked for my help.
我参与这件事纯粹是因为警方需要我的协助
Why would the police come to you？
警方为什么寻求你的帮助？
I did write the definitive book on the Woodsboro murders.
我写了一本关于伍兹伯勒谋杀案的权威书籍
I'm sure you just can't wait to write another one.
我肯定你等不及要写另一本了
What about you？What about me？
你呢？我什么？
You said you'd never leave Woodsboro.
你说你不会离开伍兹伯勒
「The only place that's real.」
「唯一让你感觉真实的地方」
But now you're here。Not with me.
但你现在在这儿 却不是和我在一起
Dewey，I took care of you.
杜威 我照顾过你
I waited until you were well，but I couldn't stay there.
我一直等到你身体有所好转 但我不能待在那种地方
It was like dog years.
这就像是狗年
One year in Woodsboro is like seven anywhere else.
伍兹伯勒一年发生的事就像别的地方七年发生的事
So it's off to Paris for a week？
所以你就去巴黎一星期？
New York for a month？L.A。forever？
去纽约一个月？永远待在洛杉矶？
It was fucking 60 Minutes II。I couldn't say no.
那是因为60分钟II这个节目我没理由拒绝
I could've been the next Diane Sawyer.
否则我不可能成为下一个黛安·索耶
What's wrong with just being Gale Weathers？
就做回真正的盖尔·韦瑟斯有什么不好？
I liked her.
我就喜欢这样的你
It didn't work，Dewey.
不可能的 杜威
We tried。We're different.
我们曾经试过 但我们是不同类型的人
You used to say that was our strength.
你以前说那是我们的优点
Well… Here you go。Thank you.
嗯… 咖啡来了 谢谢
Dewey，you're not just here because of that secondrate KMart，
杜威 你来这儿不只是为了能在二级市场
straighttovideo version of me，are you？
或是盗版小影院看见我 不是吗？
Brace yourself，Gale。All of this is actually not about you.
省省吧 盖尔 我做这些事和你没任何关系
All of what，Dewey？
所有什么事 杜威？
You do know something，don't you？Off the record？
你知道什么 是不是？不能记录？
Always.
当然
Two months ago，the Woodsboro police got a call from a woman…
两个月前 伍兹伯勒警局接到一个女人的来电…
who said she was with Stab 3.
她自称是杀戮3剧组的
She wanted to see the file on Sid，
她想看看西德妮的档案
「for research.」 And？
说是为了「研究人物内心」 然后？
The boys said no。And she wouldn't give her name.
那个接电话的同事说不行 那个女的也没留下姓名
A month later，the station gets broken into.
一个月后 警局被人闯入
The file room gets ransacked.
档案室被洗劫一空
And someone stole Sid's file？
有人偷了西德妮的档案？
I already removed it.
我早就把它转存到别的地方了
I think someone on the film is tryin' to find Sid.
我认为剧组里有人想找到西德妮
I'm sorry，this is incredible。I said，「off the record.」
对不起 这真是难以置信 我说了：「不得记录」
Right.
好吧
It's Jennifer。She needs me.
是珍妮弗 她找我
Jennifer？Gotta run.
珍妮弗？得走了
Wait！Dewey，where are you going？I'm on duty.
等等！杜威 你去哪？我在当值
Stop following me.
别跟着我
I happen to be working for the police，damn it！
我是在为警方工作 该死的！
You're not a detective，Gale Neither are you，Mr。Incognito.
你可不是警察 你也不是 匿名先生
Uh，you left your motor running。Damn it.
呃 你的车还没熄火 该死
Fans，I can handle。Fans，they want a picture，
粉丝我能有很多粉丝粉丝们 想要照片
they want a conversation.
他们想要和我交谈
I can handle fans！You see this，Dewey？
我能有很多粉丝！你看到了 杜威？
I haven't had one of these in a year and a half。Someone's gonna pay for this.
我一年半没得到过这种待遇了 有人必须为此负责
Jennifer，settle down。What happened？I'm with him.
珍妮弗 冷静 出什么事了？我和他一起来的
You。Like I'm ever going to win an award playing you.
你 似乎我一直没赢过你
There's been a second murder。Who？
第二起凶杀案发生了 谁遇害了？
Sarah Darling。Where？
莎拉·达玲 在哪？
At the studio。Where？Nancy Drew wants to know where！
摄影棚 哪？南茜·德鲁想知道在哪！
Cotton Weary。Sarah Darling。Don't you get it？
卡顿·威瑞 莎拉·达玲 难道你还不明白？
Someone's killing them in the order they die in the movie.
有人要杀他们是应为他们在电影中就会死去
Dewey，who gets killed third？
杜威 谁会是第三个死者？
Who gets killed third？
谁会是第三个死者？
You do.
就是你
I get killed in Stab 3？I get killed？Yeah.
我在杀戮3中会被杀？我会被杀？是的
Dewey，where are you going？I have to get something from my trailer.
杜威 你去哪？我去拖车里拿点东西
You live here with her？
你和她一起住这儿？
Yeah。Oh，my God！
没错 哦 天啊！
I needed a place to stay，and she said she liked having me around.
我要找个地方落脚 她说她喜欢我在她附近的感觉
Why？
为什么？
She says I make her feel safe.
她说我能让她感到安全感
She says I'm her rock。Her rock？
她说我是她的后盾 她的后盾？
Yeah。If you weren't so concerned with pretensions and appearances，
是的 如果你不是那么在意虚荣和外表
you'd be able to appreciate the positivity and emotional centeredness I provide a woman.
你就该欣赏我为一个女人所带去的乐观的精神和情绪
Stone，I'm headed to the crime scene.
斯通 我直接去犯罪现场
You stay by Jennifer's side。I suggest a search of the grounds.
你待在珍妮弗的身边 建议你清查一下四周
Hey，Dewdrop。Can I have a word？
嘿 杜威 能和你说两句吗？
Just so we can be straight。I'm a professional celebrity guard here.
直说吧 我是一名职业的保安
My resume lists Julia Roberts，
我曾经保护过朱莉亚·罗伯茨
Salmon Rushdie，Posh Spice.
塞尔门·拉什迪 时髦辣妹组合
You are the Hollywood，uh，hangeroner.
你是好莱坞演员的跟班
'Cause you're just no good as a cop anymore.
因为你不是名真正的警察
Your resume reads like the obituaries.
你的简历听起来像讣告
So how 'bout you take suggestions from me？All right？
所以你听听我的意见怎么样？好吗？
Whatever you say.
说吧
Hmm。Same deal？Found with the body？
嗯 同样的手法？在尸体边上找到？
Yeah，Maureen Prescott again。This is great.
是的 还是莫琳·普莱斯柯特 太棒了
Ten more murders and we can publish a calendar.
在发生十起凶杀案我们就能出本挂历了
The old 「killer playing with the cops」 routine.
老套的「猫和老鼠」 游戏
Very Hannibal Lecter。Very Seven.
很像汉尼拔 很像七宗罪
Doesn't the killer come after the cops in those movies？
那些杀手不是冲着电影里的警察去的？
Usually one cop makes it.
通常有一个警察能逃出生天
And？One cop doesn't.
然后？另一个下了地狱
Usually.
通常来说
Detective Kincaid，what do we know？Same killer？
金凯德警长 我们有什么线索？同一个凶手？
Hey，hey，Terminal Entertainment，this is a crime scene，okay？
嘿 嘿 终极娱乐 这是犯罪现场明白吗？
Wallace，Miss Weathers is working with me now。Thank you，Detective.
华莱士 韦瑟斯小姐目前协助我调查 谢谢 警长
You're welcome。Well，in that case，
别客气 既然如此
I'm gonna go dust for fingerprints with Jane Pauley.
我要追查灰尘上留下的简波利的指纹
Photos，Wallace，please？Thank you.
照片 华莱士麻烦了？谢谢
New pictures，same person。Anything turn up on your research yet？
新的照片 同一个人 你那边的调查有什么进展？
Nothing that will help with these.
那些东西毫无帮助
What about police around Jennifer？She's the next one to get killed in the script.
珍妮弗身边的警察呢？她是剧本中第三个被杀的人
She has a bodyguard。Besides，there were three different versions of the script.
她有个保镖 更何况 光剧本就有三个不同的版本
Something about trying to keep the ending off the Internet.
似乎是为了防止影片的结尾提前在网上泄漏
You should know that.
你应该知道
You're the technical advisor，right？
你是技术顾问 对吗？
Three versions。Three different characters die next.
三个版本 三个不同的角色接下去将面临死亡
And we don't know which one the killer read.
并且我们不知道凶手看的是哪种剧本
Hey，hold up.
嘿 等等
All I ever wanted to do was make a real classic love story.
我一直想做的是一部经典的爱情片
The studio said they'd let me.
电影公司向我许诺
I just had to do a scary movie for them first.
但是在此之前他们要我先拍一部恐怖片
Now we're shut down and I am fucked！
现在我们的电影流产了我也被炒了！
God，it's not the end of the world，Roman.
上帝保佑 这不是世界末日 罗曼
That is so easy for you to say。You can always go back to Must See TV.
你说的倒是轻巧 你还可以回去非看不可电视台
I have no movie.
我可就没电影拍了
I'm about to turn 30，and it looks like I'm the next target.
我就快30岁了 看起来下一个目标应该是我
What？You？
什么？你？
Why you？Do you think this wasn't a message？
为什么是你？你认为这不是一个信息吗？
Roman Bridger？
罗曼·布雷吉？
What？Mr。Bridger，you didn't tell us you spoke…
什么事？布雷吉先生 你对我们隐瞒了…
with Sarah Darling before she was murdered.
你在莎拉·达玲死前和她通过电话的事
Spoke with her when？
什么时侯和她通话？
The guard said she was here for a meeting with you.
警卫说她来这儿是为了和你见面的
What meeting？I don't…
什么见面？我不…
We talked with her roommate.
我们和她室友谈过
Says you called Sarah，told her to come to the studio.
说你打电话给莎拉 告诉她去摄影棚
Roommate answered the phone。Says it was you.
室友接的电话 说那个人就是你
Wait a minute。I never called her。I never told her to go anywhere.
等等 我从没打电话给她 我也没通知她去过任何地方
Roommate says she knows your voice，Mr。Bridger.
室友说她知道是你的声音 布雷吉先生
She wasn't speaking with me！God！Look.
她根本没和我通话！天啊！看呐
I did not call Sarah Darling.
我没有打电话给莎拉·达玲
Sarah Darling said you did。Someone's trying to ruin my movie.
莎拉·达玲说就是你 有人想毁了我这部电影
Someone wants to kill my movie！
有人想让这部电影流产！
We'll talk about your movie at the station。All right.
回警局再谈你的电影吧 好吧
This is the scene where you come with us.
现在是你该配合我们的工作
Dewey，Jennifer… Wait a minute.
杜威 珍妮弗… 等等
She wasn't talking with me on the phone。I'm coming！
她根本没和我通话 我自己会走！
I'll call him in。Battery.
我会再打电话给他 没电了
Mr。Riley，do you have a cell phone I can borrow？
莱利先生 能借用一下你的手机吗？
Yeah.
好的
Thank you.
谢谢
God。Roman.
天啊罗曼
Remind me not to sleep with him again.
提醒我再也不要和他同床共枕了
Come here，Cherokee.
过来 切罗基
California Women's Crisis Counseling。My name is Laura.
加利福尼亚女性生活危机辅导 我是罗拉
How can I help you？
有什么能帮你的？
Oh，Laura。I do have a crisis.
哦 劳拉 我确实有个大问题
Okay，whatever it is，you can tell me.
好了 不管是什么事 你都可以向我倾诉
Oh，my God。I've killed someone，Laura
哦 上帝啊我杀了人 罗拉
Are you sure？Uhhuh，I'm sure.
你说真的？嗯 是真的
I killed someone，I know it！Oh，my God.
我杀了人 我杀了他！哦 天啊
Well，then… I did.
嗯 那么… 我杀了人
Then the people you need to call are the police.
那你应该打电话给警方
No，I need to call you！Just you.
不 我要打给你！就是你没错
I'm sorry，your… your voice…
抱歉 你… 你的声音…
Don't you wanna know how you can help，Laura？
你不是想知道你在帮助谁吗 罗拉？
Are you listening to me？Huh？
你在听吗？啊？
Who is this？It's Mother，Laura.
你是谁？是妈妈 罗拉
Now，be a good girl and turn on the news.
现在 乖乖的把电视打开看新闻
Do as Mother tells you！
照妈妈的话做！
You're not my mother。How did you get this number？Who is this？
你不是我妈妈 你怎么知道这个号码的？你是谁？
You know your mother's voice when you hear it！
你听到这声音就该知道这是你妈妈了！
Now，turn on the news！
现在 打开电视看新闻！
And with a second cast member murdered，Stab 3
在第二名演职人员被杀之后 杀戮3
has been officially shut down，prompting those involved
官方宣布电影停拍 这当中隐隐看出
to hope and pray that these killings may be over.
制片方希望这凶杀案能有个了结
Just one question.
只有一个问题
Do you think it's over，Sidney？Do you？
你认为这事情结束了吗 西德妮？结束了吗？
Is this a wrap party or is this a wrap party？
这是杀青晚会还是杀青晚会就是这样？
Scene 34。「Maureen's Murder Flashback.」
场景34 「莫琳谋杀案重现」
I never liked that scene。That's 'cause you weren't in it.
我一直不喜欢这个场景 那是因为你没入戏
Scenes 40 through 47.
场景40跳至场景47
「The Prescott House Flashbacks。」 Tom，stop it.
「普莱斯柯特家重现」 汤姆 停下
You're scaring me。Two people are dead.
你令我很惊慌 已经死了两个人了
Scaring you？Ha！Give the sweet，young ingenue act a rest.
吓你？嘿！收起你那副甜美到无邪的样子
You're drunk。I'm coping.
你醉了 我清醒的很
I bet she fought and clawed for that Sidney part.
我敢打赌她正为西德妮这个角色而惶恐不安
I bet she stepped on any poor girl that got in her way.
我打赌她对所有阻挡她发展的可怜女孩都会冷酷无情
So you asked her out and she said no？
这么说来你要她不要参与其中但是她拒绝了？
That has nothing to do with it.
我是无能为力了
Right。Come on，Dewey.
好了 过来 杜威
Scene 50。「Dewey Saves the Day.」
场景50 「杜威的壮举」
She's so focused on success she never thinks about who she's hurting to get it.
她总是将成功建立在对别人的伤害之上
And you saved her life，like，how many times？
你还救过她 几次来着？
Gale wants the whole world to love her.
盖尔希望全世界都围着她转
One person's never enough。She's a dreamer.
一个人是远远不够的 她是个幻想家
No，she's a narcissistic，psycho bitch。No，she's not.
不 她是个自我陶醉的人 变态的婊子 不 她不是
She's got a good heart。She does.
她心肠很好 真的
She just hides it away
她只是将内心的柔软藏了起来
because she thinks people see that as weak.
因为她认为人们会把那看作是软弱的表现
This is a good picture of you。You look just like her.
你这张照片很漂亮 你和她很像
God，Dewey.
天啊杜威
You make it sound like you're still in love with her.
听起来你好像还很爱她
And I left out the part that she's cruel…
当然她还有残酷…
and selfish，obsessive and annoying.
自私 占有欲极强和脾气暴躁的一面
We have one Gale Weathers here。We don't need two.
这里已经有一位盖尔·韦瑟斯了 不需要第二个
Hey，Dewdrop，got your girlfriend out here.
嘿 杜威 把你的女朋友带走
Look who I found slinkin' around the yard。The nightly news.
我发现她在院子里鬼鬼祟祟的 一件夜间新闻
I wasn't slinking。I was walking.
我没有鬼鬼祟祟 我刚好走过
You were eavesdropping at the bedroom window.
你在卧室窗外偷听
Yeah，a bedroom that you seemed awfully at home in.
对 这屋子里看起来很可怕的一间卧室
All right，let's talk.
好吧 我们谈谈
Come on.
走
What's this about，Gale？
你玩的哪出 盖尔？
Did you know they released Roman？
你知道他们放了罗曼了吗？
Sarah's call didn't come from his cell phone.
他并没有打电话给莎拉
Where did it come from？A cloned cell phone。It's untraceable.
那电话是谁打的？一个仿制的手机 无迹可寻
Thanks for that update，Gale。Why don't you just go back home？
谢谢你带来的最新情报 盖尔 你为什么不赶快回去？
Dewey，wait a minute。Just wait one second.
杜威 等等 就一会儿
How old do you think Maureen Prescott is in this picture？
你看着照片里的莫琳·普莱斯柯特有多大？
Nineteen，twenty.
19或者20岁吧
That's what I thought，so I checked it out.
我也是这么想的 所以我去查了一下
I cannot find any information about her at this age.
我找不到她在这个年龄段的任何记录
I mean，nothing.
我的意思是 记录一片空白
She lived in Woodsboro her whole life。Someone there must know something.
她一直住在伍兹伯勒 肯定有人知道些什么
Almost her whole life.
她的一生
Two years before she met Sidney's father，she left Woodsboro.
在她遇到西德妮父亲的两年前 她离开过伍兹伯勒
No one has any idea where she went or what she did.
没人知道她去哪了或是去干了什么
It's like she fell into a black hole，Dewey！She vanished！
就好像她去了一个黑洞 杜威！她消失了！
So？So？
然后？然后？
Why is the killer leaving pictures of Maureen？
为什么凶手要留下莫琳的照片？
And why these pictures at that point in her life？
还有为什么这些照片刚好是那个时间段的？
I don't know！
我不知道！
If I thought like a homicidal maniac，
如果我的想法和变态杀人狂一样
then I'd know how a homicidal maniac thinks.
那我就能知道变态杀人狂的想法
What？
怎么了？
Jennifer。Jennifer？
珍妮弗 珍妮弗？
Look at the buildings.
看那建筑
The second story。There and there.
看二楼 那儿和那儿
It's the same！It's the same street 28 years ago.
一模一样！这两处28年前是同一条街
Oh，my God。Maureen Prescott was at the back lot at Sunrise Studios！
哦 天啊莫琳·普莱斯柯特当时就在升阳电影公司
Oh，my God。I gotta make some calls.
哦 天啊 我得联系几个人
Steven Stone Protection Services.
史蒂文·斯通保安服务
Stone，where are you？
斯通 你在哪？
I'm just checking your tin can，Dewdrop.
我在检查你的罐头 杜威
Well，come back inside and stay with Jennifer.
好的 回到里面和珍妮弗待在一起
Something's happened。I have to go to the police.
有事发生了 我要去警局一趟
Is that an order，Dewdrop？'Cause Steven Stone doesn't work for you.
这是命令吗 杜威？可是史蒂文·斯通可不为你工作
Get back in the house。Would I call you if it wasn't important？
回到屋子里去 如果不是十万火急我会打给你吗？
What are you doing in there anyway？
那你在做什么呢？
Me？I'm just checking to make sure there's no killer in here…
我？我检查一下确保这里没有杀手…
waitin' to off you like he did your little sister.
等着像杀你妹妹那样杀了你
What did you say？I can't believe you said that.
你说什么？真不敢相信这活从你嘴里说出来
That makes me…
那让我…
Angry！
很生气！
Fucker！
畜生！
Gotta call Kincaid.
必须打给金凯德
Dewey，where is everybody？
杜威 人都哪去了？
Oh.
哦
Oh，God。Jennifer？
哦 老天 珍妮弗？
Angelina？Tom？
安吉莉娜？汤姆？
Oh，God！What happened？
哦 老天！出什么事了？
Ohh！
哦！
Don't do that。I'm overreacting.
别这样 我太敏感了
Dewdrop？
杜威？
Stone？Oh，my God！
斯通？哦 天啊！
Oh，God，Stone！
哦 天啊斯通！
Oh，God！
哦 天啊！
Dewey，is he dead？Yeah.
杜威 他死了吗？是的
Everyone back inside！
所有人都回去！
It's all right。Don't panic.
没事了 别紧张
Okay，outside。Everyone，stay together and try to remain calm.
好吧 出去 所有人待在一起保持冷静
It's not mine。Not mine.
不是我的电话 也不是我的
Shit！It's the fax.
该死！是传真
「Interior，Jennifer's house。Living room，night.」
「室内 珍妮弗的房子 客厅 晚上」
It's a script page.
这是一个剧本的脚本
W… What's it say？
它… 它说什么了？
「With the bodyguard stabbed，the five stand trapped.」
「在保安被杀之后 其他五个人掉入了陷阱中」
He's rewriting the movie。「As the killer waits outside，
他在重写电影 「凶手在外面伺机而动
suddenly the fax machine sends news of their fates.「
突然间传真机发来了决定他们命运的一纸宣言「
It's a trick！Everybody outside！
这是陷阱！所有人出去！
Outside where he can pick us off one by one？
出去让他能把我们一个个的给宰了？
「The killer prepares to grant mercy to only one of them.」
「凶手只准备放过他们其中一个」
Don't you get it？
你们还不明白吗？
The killer says he's outside because he wants us here inside.
凶手说他就在外面因为他要我们待在屋子里
Which one is it？Come on！
他会放过谁？快点！
「Who will survive？
「谁能活下来？
Is it Jennifer？Tom？Angelina？Dewey？Gale？
是珍妮弗？汤姆？安吉丽娜？杜威？盖尔？
The killer will give mercy to…「 Everyone outside！
杀手将会放过…「 所有人出去！
He grants mercy to who？I wanna know what happens！
他会放过谁？我想知道事情会怎么样！
Wait for the fucking movie！
等这该死的电影上映！
I've gotta know！I'm goin' back in！No.
我必须要知道！我回去！不
All right，everyone，back。Stay together.
好吧 所有人 回去 待在一起
What's it say？And the…
上面说什么？那个…
killer will give mercy to…
凶手会放过…
whoever… Whoever？
任何一个人… 任何一个人？
Piece of shit.
放屁
「Whoever… Whoever smells the…」
「任何… 任何一个闻到燃气的人…」
I can't stop rolling down the hill！
我要滚下山了！
Gale！Jennifer！
盖尔！珍妮弗！
Dewey！Dewey！
杜威！杜威！
Dewey，where are you？
杜威 你在哪儿？
Over here，Dewey！
这边 杜威！
Dewey！Gale！
杜威！盖尔！
Gale，behind you！
盖尔 你后面！
Dewey！Are you all right？
杜威！你还好吗？
Yeah，never been better.
是的 好的不能再好了
Yeah，I'm all right。Where'd he go？
好的 我也没事 他去哪儿了？
He must've rolled under the car。All right，stay close.
他滚到车下去了 好了 跟紧我
Is he back there？
他在车后吗？
No。No？
没有 没有？
He's fast。Could've sworn I hit him.
他动作很快 不能保证我打中他了
Are you all right？
你没事吧？
Yeah.
是的
Thanks for saving me.
谢谢你救了我
Ah，it's habit.
啊习惯了
Oh，God.
哦 天啊
What the fuck…
你该死的…
happened to you？
到底是怎么回事？
Jennifer，wait a minute。Who gave you a place to stay？
珍妮弗 等等 谁给你地方落脚的？
Who are you supposed to be protecting？Jennifer！
你应该保护谁？珍妮弗！
Hey！
嘿！
My lawyer liked that.
我的律师会让你们后悔的
Not as much as I did.
我也是
Angelina？
安吉丽娜？
Tom was in the house。How'd you end up way over there？
汤姆在房子里 你怎么从那儿走来？
Oh，my God！Tom was in the house！
哦 天啊！汤姆在屋子里！
Are we safe？
我们安全吗？
Safe from who？
有什么不安全的？
Wait a second！
等等！
Another picture.
又一张照片
I killed her.
我杀了她
Whoever it is
不管谁是凶手
is now taking credit for Maureen Prescott's murder.
他正在算莫琳·普莱斯柯特谋杀案的那笔账
But we know who killed Maureen Prescott.
但我们已经知道是谁杀了莫琳·普莱斯柯特
Billy Loomis and Stu Macher.
是比利·鲁米斯和斯图·马彻尔
They even told Sidney how they did it.
他们甚至还告诉西德妮他们是怎么做的
Yeah，but if I'm not mistaken，
是的 但是如果我没记错的话
you said in your book that Sidney got it wrong once before.
你在你的书里说过西德妮曾经搞错过一次
She accused Cotton Weary of murdering her mother.
她指控卡顿·威瑞谋杀了她妈妈
He was sent away for it。Maybe there is a third killer.
但他最后被证明无罪释放了 也许真的有第三个凶手
Sidney might know something。I told you。I don't know where Sidney is.
西德妮也许知道什么 我说了 我不知道西德妮在哪
And even if there was a third killer，Sidney doesn't know about it.
而且就算有第三个凶手 西德妮也不可能知道这件事
That is for me to decide。I need to talk to her。She's a key element in this case.
这事我说了算 我要和她谈谈 她是这件案子的关键
I have a press conference in an hour.
一个小时后我有一个新闻发布会
I need to explain why there are three dead celebrities and a bodyguard.
我要解释为什么会死了三个演艺明星和一个保镖
And a very angry mayor.
还要应付气极了的市长
Look，we all know this has something to do with Stab 3.
听着 我们都知道这和杀戮3有关
But what we do not know is why the killer keeps leaving pictures…
但我们不知道凶手为什么一直留下照片…
of Maureen Prescott taken over 25 years ago.
还是莫琳·普莱斯柯特25年前的照片
And the photographs taken at the same studio Stab 3 is shooting out of.
而且照片上的背景和杀戮3的取景一模一样
What does this have to do with Sid？
这和西德妮有什么关系？
Who knows more about Maureen Prescott than her own daughter？
谁能比西德妮更了解她妈妈？
Sid's dad couldn't help you and he was married to Maureen.
西德妮的爸爸不可能帮助你因为他和莫琳结婚了
What's your problem？Last night you were almost charcoal.
你是怎么回事？昨晚你差点变成一块焦炭
You gonna help us or what？
你是想帮助我们还是怎么样？
Do you wanna have this conversation with a polygraph？
你想我拿测谎仪来测试你吗？
Is that a threat？When it's a threat，you'll know it.
这算是威胁吗？当这是个威胁的时候 你会知道的
Was that a threat？
这是威胁吗？
Boys，boys！Why don't we compare our gun calibers later？
伙计们 伙计们！我们就不能先好好谈谈？
The issue is Maureen Prescott.
焦点就是莫琳·普莱斯柯特
Wrong。The issue is Sidney Prescott.
不是 焦点是西德妮·普莱斯柯特
And either Mr。Riley is going to obstruct justice or put me in touch with her.
而莱利先生现在要阻碍案件调查并且阻止我们接触她
So… where is she？
那么… 她在哪？
Hi，you've reached the machine。Leave a message。Talk as long as you want.
嗨 这是留言信箱 留下口讯 想说多久都没关系
Sid，it's me。This is the fifth time I've called.
西德妮 是我 这是我第五个电话了
Please pick up。I wanna make sure you're okay.
拜托你快接起来吧 我想知道你很安全
Sid！
西德妮！
Dewey.
杜威
What are you doing down here？
你在这儿干嘛？
Oh！Actually，what was I doing up there？
哦！是啊我来这儿干嘛呢？
Jesus，Dewey，are you okay？
天啊杜威 你还好吧？
Yeah，I'm all right.
是的 我没事
Is she all right？Hey，you know Gale。It'd take a direct hit.
她还好吗？嘿 你知道盖尔这个人 真是一语中的
So the news said this was the precinct.
新闻说案件发生在这里的管区
Who's this guy Kincaid？
谁是那个叫金凯德的家伙？
Come here.
跟我来
I told you to stay hidden。It's not safe for you to be here.
我告诉你好好躲起来的 你现在来这儿不安全
The killer called me。What？
凶手打电话给我了 什么？
Yeah，he found me。I'm no more safe there than I am here，
是的 他发现我了 我在这儿反而更安全
and at least here I'm not alone.
至少在这儿我不会孤单
Okay，come on.
好吧 来
Detective Kincaid？Yeah.
金凯德警长？是的
There's someone here who wants to help.
有人希望能对案件调查起到帮助
Oh，my God。Sidney.
哦 天啊西德妮
Is the man fast or what？
是人们动作变快了还是？
Hi。Hi，Gale.
嗨 嗨 盖尔
I'm glad you're all right。Thank you.
很高兴你没事 谢谢
Sid，this is Detective Kincaid.
西德妮 这是金凯德警长
Nice to finally meet you，Sidney.
很高兴总算见到你了 西德妮
The killer called her.
凶手打电话给她了
What？When？What did he say？
什么？什么时候？他说什么了？
Oh，you know，the usual small talk。What's new，
哦 你知道 和以前一样的威胁 有什么新鲜的
how you been，how do you wanna die？
你怎么样 你想怎么个死法？
Sidney，do you have any idea how he could've gotten your number？
西德妮 你有想过他是怎么知道你的号码的吗？
He could have monitored her calls on a scanner.
他可能是用扫描仪在监视她的通话
Did you call her from the set？
你用座机打给她过吗？
No。Do you have her number stored in your memory？
没有 你有她号码的记录吗？
Phone memory！Oh。Yeah，guess I do.
通话记录！哦 是的 我想是的
Has anyone else ever used your phone？Just Jennifer.
有任何曾经使用过你的手机吗？就珍妮弗了
And you.
还有你
Hey，I'm the cop here。You're in my office，Riley.
嘿 我是这儿的警察 你在我的办公室里 莱利
The killer leaves a photograph after each murder，Sidney.
凶手在每一起凶杀案之后都会留下一张照片 西德妮
They were taken in Hollywood at the same studio that they're shooting Stab 3.
照片都是在杀戮3设在好莱坞的摄影棚拍摄的
Why didn't you tell me？This is my mother，Dewey.
你为什不告诉我？这是我妈妈 杜威
Why didn't you say something？
你为什么什么都不说？
I was afraid they were bait。Something to，you know，trick you out of hiding.
我害怕它们是诱饵 有些事 你知道 想把你引出来
Sidney，was she an actress or a model？
西德妮 她曾经是个演员还是模特？
They look a lot like publicity stills.
它们看起来很像宣传照
I，uh，don't know.
我 嗯 不知道
Detective，I wanna see this place in the pictures.
警长 我想去看看照片里的这个地方
Are you sure？Absolutely.
你确定？是的
Slow it down。Sorry.
慢点 抱歉
Watch the fuckin' aliens.
小心那个该死的外星人
I'm gonna go talk to the studio brass about those photos.
我去和公司老总谈谈这些照片的问题
Yeah，right。I know where you're goin'.
好的 去吧 我知道那个地方
Keep an eye on Sidney。I know where you're goin'.
注意西德妮 我知道你去哪
You're gonna get her some flowers and candy，huh？Huh？
你打算给她买一些花和糖果 嗯？呃？
Gimme a break。Yeah，gimme a call.
放过我吧 好的 保持联系
Just keep your eye on her.
小心保护她
That stairwell over there，that's where one of the pictures was taken.
那个楼梯就在那儿 其中一张照片拍摄的地方
I can't believe she never mentioned any of this。Dewey！
我不敢相信她从没提过这些事 杜威！
Sorry。Martha！
抱歉 玛莎！
Oh，my God，Sidney。Hey，hold it right there！
哦 天啊西德妮 嘿 待在那儿别动！
Don't shoot。I'm only 17。It's okay。We know her.
别开枪 我只有17岁 没事 是熟人
We do？
是吗？
Tell me that's his exgirlfriend，I'll shoot myself.
如果你和我说这是他的前女友 我就开枪崩了自己
It's Martha Meeks，Randy's sister.
这是玛莎·米克斯 兰迪的妹妹
Randy's sister？Yeah，can't you tell？
兰迪的妹妹？是的 你认不出来吗？
We miss you in Woodsboro guys.
我们伍兹伯勒的朋友很想你
Martha，what are you doing here？
玛莎 你在这儿干嘛呢？
There's something you guys should see.
有些东西你们得看看
Told ya I'd make a movie someday。Huh？
早就说了我总有一天会拍一部电影的 嗯？
Oh，my God.
哦天啊
Well，if you're watching this tape，
好吧 如果你们看到这片子
it means，as I feared，I did not survive these killings
这就意味着 我挂了 没能在温莎大学
here at Windsor College，and that giving up my virginit
这场屠杀中幸存下来 还有把我的贞操献给了
to Karen Kolchak at the video store was probably not a good idea.
影碟店的凯伦·高尔察克也许不是个好主意
Karen Kolchak？Yes，Karen Kolchak.
凯伦·高尔察克？是的 凯伦·高尔察克
「Creepy Karen」？Shut up！
「疯子凯伦」？闭嘴！
She's a sweet person，okay？We were working late.
她是个小甜妞 好吗？我们通常工作到恨晚
We were putting away some videos in the porno section，and，you know，shit happens.
我们把一些色情片整理好 然后 你们知道 做那事了
Open the door，Randy！Fifteen minutes.
开门 兰迪！15分钟
It's my room too！
这也是我的房间！
Paul，15 minutes。I'm leaving my legacy.
保罗 给我15分钟 我在留下我的遗物
Fifteen minutes，Paul！Damn！
就15分钟 保罗！去死！
Anyway，the reason I'm here is to help you…
闲话少说 我是来帮助你们的…
so that my death will not be in vain.
这样对我的死也不会毫无价值
That my life's work will help save some other poor soul from getting mutilated.
我用生命换来的工作将会挽救很多可怜的人
If this killer does come back，
如果凶手真的回来的
and he's for real，there are a few things that you gotta remember.
那么他就是来真的 有几件事你们要记住
Is this simply another sequel？
这只是简单的续集吗？
Well，if it is，same rules apply.
嗯 如果是的话 那么规则相通
But，here's the critical thing.
但是 关键就在这里
If you find yourself dealing with an unexpected backstory，
如果你们发现自己是在经历一个完全陌生的背景故事
and a preponderance of exposition，then the sequel rules do not apply.
和一大堆的说明 那续集的规则就不适用
Because you're not dealing with the sequel。You are dealing with…
因为你们经历的不是续集 你们经历的是…
the concluding chapter of a trilogy.
三部曲的终章
Trilogy。That's right。It's a rarity in the horror field，
三部曲 是的 这是一个罕见的恐怖领域
but it does exist，and it is a force to be reckoned with.
但它确实存在 而且它是一股不可忽视的力量
Because true trilogies are about going back to the beginning and discovering something…
因为真正的三部曲最终是会回到原点并发现某些事的
that wasn't true from the getgo.
那从一开始就不是真的
Godfather，Jedi，all revealed something that we thought was true that wasn't true.
教父 绝境 我们认为是真的但那未必是真的
So if it is a trilogy you are dealing with，
所以如果你们经历的三部曲
here are some super trilogy rules.
这里有一些超级三部曲的规则
One：You've got a killer who's gonna be superhuman.
第一：你们面对的是个超级杀手
Stabbing him won't work。Shooting him won't work.
用刀桶他没用 用枪打他也没用
Basically，in the third one，
基本来说 第三步
you've gotta cryogenically freeze his head，decapitate him，
你必须冻住他的头 把他的头砍下来
or blow him up.
或者一枪打爆他的头
Number two：Anyone，including the main character，can die.
第二：任何人 包括主角 都会死亡
This means you，Sid.
这就意味着是你 西德妮
I'm sorry。It's the final chapter.
抱歉 这是终章了
It could be fuckin' 「Reservoir Dogs」 by the time this thing is through.
事情可不会演变成电影「落水狗」里那种简单的仇杀
Number three：The past will come back to bite you in the ass.
第三：过去的事会死咬着不放
Whatever you think you know about the past，forget it.
不管你认为自己有多了解过去 忘了它
The past is not at rest！
过去的事可没有放弃对你的追逐！
Any sins you think were committed in the past are about to break out and destroy you.
你认为什么都已消散的罪恶即将爆发并吞噬你
So in closing，let me say…
所以我私下告诉你们 祝你们…
good luck，Godspeed，
好运 上帝与你们同在
and for some of you，I'll see you soon.
每个人都一样 你们很快就能见到我
'Cause the rules say some of you ain't gonna make it。I didn't.
因为规则上说了你们中间有人过不了这关 就比如我
Not if you're watching this tape.
否则你们就不会看到这盘带子了
Thank you.
谢谢
You be careful。Say hi to your folks.
你要小心点 代我像你家人问好
You be careful too，Sid.
你也要小心 西德妮
Bye，Dewey。Come visit us soon.
再见 杜威 早点来看看我们
I will，Martha。Thank you。Bye.
我会的 玛莎 谢谢你 再见
I've got an idea。I'll hook up with you guys later。Want us to come with you？
我有点事 稍后和你们联系 要我们一起去吗？
I work better alone.
我一个人更方便
And why don't you try to figure out where those other pictures were taken？
你们为什么不去找出其他照片是在哪儿拍的？
I can see nothing's changed。Nah.
看得出来她没什么变化 是的
Oh，shit.
哦 该死
Hello？
有人吗？
Jeez。What the hell are you doing？
天啊 你在这干嘛？
Being Gale Weathers。What the hell are you doing？
扮演盖尔·韦瑟斯 你在这干嘛？
I am Gale Weathers.
我才是盖尔·韦瑟斯
Here's how I see it.
我是这么想的
I've got no house，no bodyguard，no movie，
我现在没有房子 没有保镖 没电影可拍
and I'm being stalked.
而且正在被追杀
Because someone wants to kill me？No，because someone wants to kill you.
因为有人想杀我？不 因为有人想杀你
And now。Starting now，I go where you go.
从现在开始 你去哪我去哪
That way，if someone wants to kill me，I'll be with you.
那样的话 如果有人想杀我 我会拖着你
And since they really want to kill you，
而且如果他们真的想杀你
they won't kill me，they'll kill you.
那他们就不会杀我 他们将会杀你
Make sense？None.
明白了吗？不明白
You know，in the movies I play you as being much smarter.
你知道 我在电影中扮演的你比你本人聪明多了
And as a sane person。For you，that must be quite a stretch.
就像个很理智的人 对你来说 这种表演技巧很容易
That's funny。Ha！
真有趣 哈！
Need to get into that building？Yeah.
要进去？是的
Is there a story in that building？Maybe.
里面真的有什么玄机？也许吧
Gale Weathers would find a way.
盖尔·韦瑟斯会找到办法的
Bitch。All right，wait.
婊子 好吧 等等
Just… Don't tell me what to do.
只是… 别教我怎么做
Basements，wow.
地下室 哇哦
Basements creep me out.
地下室让我浑身发毛
You'd make a fascinating interview.
你会有一个神奇的采访经历
Hello？
有人吗？
Hi。Excuse me。I am Gale Weathers，
嗨 打扰一下 我是盖尔·韦瑟斯
and I'm here researching with the police… this photo.
我正在协助警察调查… 这张照片
It was taken at the studio.
看起来像在摄影棚拍的
Her name is Maureen Prescott。Back then it was Roberts.
她叫莫琳·普莱斯柯特 当时叫罗伯茨
Hey，are you… No.
嘿 你… 不
But you look just… Like her？
但是你看起来… 像她？
I've been hearing it all my life.
我一辈子都在听她的名字
It's uncanny。I was up for Princess Leia.
真是不可思议 我可是准备成为莱娅公主了
I was this close。So，who gets it？
我和她如此相像 那么谁搞到那张照片的？
The one who sleeps with George Lucas？
和乔治·卢卡斯上过床的人？
I'm sorry。I didn't mean to bring up a sore subject for you.
抱歉 我不是想揭你的伤疤的
Sure，you didn't。None of them did.
当然 你不想 没人想
So，how can I help you？
那么 我能帮你什么呢？
Or do you want me to tell you who you look like？
还是想我告诉你你长的像谁吗？
Hmph。How 'bout some information on Maureen Roberts？
哼 我想知道一些莫琳·罗伯茨的信息？
I don't work for the cops，sweetie。I work for the studio.
我可不为警察工作 甜心 我是电影公司的人
Really。Well，would you work for…
当然 嗯 你难道不是为…
the President？
总统工作？
The president… of the studio.
那也是… 电影公司的总统
Fifty dollars？
50美元？
Who are you？A reporter for Woodsboro High？
你是谁？伍兹伯勒高中来的记者？
It's worth two grand.
这个值2000美元
Are you gonna help Gale Weathers or not？
你打算帮助盖尔·韦瑟斯还是怎么样？
I know every face in here.
这儿的每个人我都认识
I got a respect for the unknown actor.
不出名的演员都很尊敬我
If they're looking for Maureen Roberts，they're never gonna find her.
如果他们是在找莫琳·罗伯茨 那他们永远也找不到
Rina Reynolds they will.
他们只能找到瑞娜·雷诺兹
Rina Reynolds.
瑞娜·雷诺兹
Stage name.
艺名
You should talk，Judy Jurgenstern.
你才需要艺名 朱迪·乔根斯坦
What are these movies？
这些是什么电影？
Amazombies，Space Psycho，Creatures from the San Andreas Fault.
亚马逊野人 空间杀人狂 圣安地列斯断层的生物
Horror pictures back in Milton's heyday.
恐怖电影在米尔顿的鼎盛时期回归
Back in what？
什么回来？
John Milton，the horror producer？Those were his movies.
约翰·米尔顿 恐怖电影制片人？那些都是他的电影
Come on，Sid.
振作 西德妮
Oh，my God！Sidney Prescott！
哦 天啊！西德妮·普莱斯柯特！
Oh，my God！I'm Angelina Tyler。I'm you！
哦 天啊！我是安吉丽·娜泰勒 我扮演的是你！
I mean，I'm not.
我的意思是 我不是
I mean，I was.
我的意思是 曾经是
I… I thought，
我… 我想
well，if there's no movie，
嗯 既然没什么电影了
no one would care if I took some souvenirs.
也就没人会在乎我拿些纪念品了
Souvenirs？
纪念品？
I may never win another role，
我没获得过别的角色
so these may be my only memories，
所以这也许是我唯一的记忆了
you know，of Hollywood.
你知道 好莱坞的记忆
I know it's weird 'cause it's your life and all，but…
我知道这有点奇怪因为这毕竟是你的生活 但是
I wanted to make you proud，Sidney.
我想让你感到骄傲 西德妮
Oh。Well，I'm sure I would've been.
哦 是的 我想我会的
The real Sidney。The real person.
真实的西德妮 真实的人
I wish…
我希望…
I wish it would've worked out.
我希望电影已经拍好了
Hey…
嘿…
Angelina？
安吉丽娜？
Hello？
有人吗？
Close call.
死里逃生
What are you doing here？
你在这儿干嘛？
It occurred to me that I've never snuck through your bedroom window.
对我来说 我从没能悄悄的从窗户爬入你的卧室
See what you do to me？
知道你对我做了什么吗？
What you've done to me.
你对我做的
About the，uh，sex stuff？
那种事情？
You know，I'm not trying to rush you at all.
你知道 我并不是想催促你
Would you settle for a PG13 relationship？
你会接收这种限制级的关系吗？
Dewey！
杜威！
Sidney，I'm in here.
西德妮 我在这儿
Over here.
这儿
Yes。Mother will protect you from the bogeyman.
是的 妈妈不会让你被那些坏人伤害的
Come into the bedroom.
来卧室
Hide in Mommy's bed.
藏在妈妈床上
I lied，Sidney。I can't protect you at all.
我说谎了 西德妮 我没有能力保护你
You don't deserve to be protected！You didn't protect me！
你不值得我保护！你都没保护我！
You did your mom a favor。That woman was a slutbag whore…
你帮了你妈妈个忙 那个女人是个下贱的妓女…
who flashed her shit all over town like she was Sharon Stone.
她在镇上水性杨花 好像自己是莎朗·斯通
'Cause let's face it，Sidney，
让我们正视这个事实 西德妮
your mother was no Sharon Stone.
你妈妈不是什么莎朗·斯通
Sidney's mother was fucking my father。Sid，where are you？
西德妮的妈妈勾引了我爸爸 西德妮 你在哪？
Dewey！Dewey，help me！
杜威！杜威 救我！
Sidney？Give Mommy a kiss and we'll make up.
西德妮？给妈妈一个吻吧 我们就能再续前缘
No！Sidney！
不！西德妮！
Sid！
西德妮！
Sid，are you okay？What happened？
西德妮 你还好吗？出什么事了？
The killer's in the house，Dewey。He's upstairs.
凶手在房子里 杜威 他在楼上
And my mother… Let's go，let's go.
还有我妈妈… 我们走 我们走
I heard her voice。I saw her，Dewey.
我听到她的声音 我看见她了 杜威
Upstairs。Come on，let's go。It's okay，Sid.
上楼 快 走 没事的 西德妮
You weren't supposed to go in that house。It's all set up for the murder scene.
你不该进那个屋子的 那都是以凶案现场为模版造的
I'm sorry you had to see that。He was in there.
很抱歉让你见到这里 他在里面
He was in there，I swear，I swear。You know I believe you.
他在里面 我发誓 我发誓 你知道我相信你
What happened？Kincaid，hey。There's nobody up here.
什么事？金凯德 嘿 这上面没人
Come on.
起来
走
Okay，so I stole the mask，whatever.
好吧 就算我偷了面具又怎么样
Didn't know you got the gas chamber for that？
难道你要把我送进毒气室？
You stole the mask？I took it.
你偷了这面具？我拿来看看
You took the mask or you stole the mask？
你拿了这面具还是偷了这面具？
I took it as like a souvenir。Don't look at me。I didn't take shit.
我把它当作纪念品拿出来的 别看我 我什么都没拿
I know he was there。I am not dreaming，I am not crazy.
我知道他在那儿 我没有做梦 也没有发疯
He was there in Woodsboro。That's not Woodsboro，Sidney.
他就在那伍兹伯勒中 那不是伍兹伯勒 西德妮
You know what I mean.
你明白我的意思
But he was there。He or she，or whoever this is.
但是他在那儿 他或者是她 不管是谁
We're gonna take you back to the station，keep you under watch.
我们会将你送回警局 保护你的安全
Put you in a safe house。Whatever it takes.
你会住在安全屋 不管发生什么
Come on.
上车
It's all right，Sid。We all believe you.
没事的 西德妮 我们都相信你
He's watching。And he wants you.
凶手在看着这一切 他想要杀的就是你
Hey，Dew。Dew.
嘿 杜威 杜威
Come on，we have to go catch up with Sid。Take a look at this first.
拜托 我们要跟上西德妮 先看看这个
Someone we know？Where'd you get this？
是不是我们认识的那个？你们哪找到的？
We got it。Archives.
我们在档案室搞到的
Sidney's mother was an actress。Three movies。Horror movies.
西德妮的妈妈演过三部电影 恐怖电影
You want to know who produced all three？Who？
你想知道导演是谁吗？谁？
There'll be other movies，Roman.
还有别的电影会开拍的 罗曼
Not only did they kill the film，but they killed my cast.
他们不但搅黄了我的电影 还杀了我的演员
Nobody's gonna want to work with me.
现在没人愿意和我合作了
Variety called me a pariah.
圈内开始把我看成不入流的小导演了
I don't even know what a pariah is.
我都不知道这不入流的导演是什么意思
Why couldn't someone have killed the cast from Stab 1？Huh？
为什么那些人不去杀杀戮1的演员？啊？
Or Stab 2？Why me？
或者是杀戮2的？为什么是我？
What… John，what did we do wrong？
为什么… 约翰 我们做错什么了？
Hollywood is full of criminals whose careers are flourishing.
好莱坞是一个极其势力的罪恶圈子
I'm not a criminal！I was questioned.
我不是个罪犯！我却被带去审问
Yeah，but that's all。I was questioned。That's it.
好的 但是就这样 我被审问了 就是这样
It's good for your mystique.
这对提升你的神秘感有好处
You think it will help me get work？
你认为这对我的工作有帮助？
Roman。John.
罗曼 约翰
Jennifer，and guests。To what do I owe the honor？
珍妮弗 还有贵客 什么风把你们给吹来了？
Rina Reynolds.
瑞娜·雷诺兹
Rina Reynolds？Who's Rina Reynolds？
瑞娜·雷诺兹？谁是瑞娜·雷诺兹？
Why don't you head to the house？
你为什么不去片场？
Tell everybody not to cut the cake without me.
让大家不用等我了 先切蛋糕吧
Oh，God，I forgot。Your birthday.
哦 天啊我忘了 今天是你的生日
Yeah，as if life isn't tragic enough。Happy birthday，Roman.
是的 看起来生活好有点盼头 生日快乐 罗曼
Shut the doors behind you，please.
关上门 谢谢
So，you knew Sidney Prescott's mother.
那么 你认识西德妮的妈妈
Who？Rina Reynolds？
谁？瑞娜·雷诺兹？
Ahh。Do you know how many actors have worked for me？
啊你知道有多少演员在我手下工作过吗？
Hundreds。Thousands.
成千上万
We didn't say she was an actor。Good catch.
我们没说她是个演员 说得好
So what's the point？Uh，no point.
那么你们到底想说什么？呃 没什么意思
I'm just gonna give Detective Kincaid a call.
我只是打算个金凯德警长打个电话
I remember。She was a bit player in a couple of my movies.
我想起来了 她好像在我的几部电影里演过小角色
A nobody。So what does it matter？
一个小角色 那又怎么样？
Oh，come on。You have made millions off the story of her murder.
哦 得了 你已经用她的谋杀案赚了上百万了
You're obsessed with her，and you're obsessed with her daughter！
当初你迷恋她 现在你迷恋她的女儿！
Easy，Geraldo。Why don't you tell us the truth？
别激动 杰拉尔多 为什么你不告诉我们真相？
What the hell are you guys getting at？
你们这些家伙都听了什么风言风语？
I make horror films，that's what I do.
我只不过是拍了几部恐怖电影
The studio came to me with Stab.
现在公司发生的凶案是冲我来的
They came to me。Check it out.
他们是冲我来的 去查查
But you knew who she was。When we did the first Stab，
但是你认识她 当我们拍第一部杀戮的时候
I realized I had known Maureen Prescott before。I mean，as Rina.
我才意识到我以前就认识莫琳·普莱斯柯特 就是瑞娜
I couldn't tell anyone。Can you imagine the press？
我不能告诉任何人 你们能想像那种压力吗？
And now？I mean，murders on your set，
那现在呢？我的意思是 你的片场发生了凶杀案
and still you say nothing？Get real.
而你还能装做没事？现实点
That would make me a suspect。Just because you knew her？
那会让我成为嫌疑人 就因为你认识她？
Yeah。I don't think so.
是的 我不这么认为
Just what did happen to Maureen when she was in Hollywood？
莫琳在好莱坞的时候到底发生了什么？
Now，you listen to me，Lois Lane.
现在 你听好了 路易斯·莱恩
Let it go。It's dead and buried.
不要再追究了 事情已经过去并被掩埋
How would you like to see it dug up on national TV？
你觉得这事在官方电视台上放出来会怎么样？
Why don't you tell me what happened？
你为什么不告诉我到底发生了什么？
It was in the '70s。Everything was different.
那是70年代的时候 一切都不同了
I was wellknown for my parties.
当时我因为我的聚会而出名
Rina knew what they were.
瑞娜知道那是怎么一回事
It was for girls like her to meet men.
那种聚会就是为了给像她那样的女孩物色男人
Men who could get them parts…
而男人也能得到…
if they made the right impression.
如果男女彼此间印象不错的话
Nothing happened to her that she didn't invite in one way or another，
她并没有被别人以这样或那样的方式邀请
no matter what she said afterwards.
不管她说了什么
Are you saying she… I'm saying things got out of hand.
你是说她… 我是说事情完全失控了
Maybe they did take advantage of her。Maybe the sad truth is…
也许他们只是利用她 也许悲惨的事实就是…
this is not the city for innocents.
这不是座无辜之城
No charges were brought。And the bottom line is…
不存在任何指控 而结果就是…
Rina Reynolds wouldn't play by the rules.
瑞娜·雷诺兹没有按规则来玩游戏
You wanna get ahead in Hollywood？
你想在好莱坞站住脚跟？
You gotta play the game，or go home.
你必须去玩这个游戏 要么你就卷铺盖回家
What do you know about trilogies？
你对三部曲知道多少？
You mean，like movie trilogies？
你是说 像电影三部曲这种的？
You seem to like movies，Detective.
你好像很喜欢电影 警长
Call me Mark，would you？'Cause I'm gonna keep calling you Sidney.
叫我马克 好吗？因为我一直叫你西德妮
I'll call you Mark when you catch the killer，Detective.
你抓到凶手我才会叫你马克 警长
All I know about movie trilogies is that in the third one…
我所知道的关于三部曲的事就是在那最后一部之中
all bets are off.
什么事情都有可能发生
Did you request this case？
你主动请求接手这个案子的吗？
No。They tend to put me on the ones that deal with the business.
不 他们更希望把我用于处理那些文职工作上
I grew up here，and I know my way around the studios.
我在这里长大 我知道在办公室的生存方式
Huh.
嗯
Must be exciting。Beautiful place，beautiful people.
肯定很有意思 漂亮的地方 友好的同事
To me，Hollywood is about death.
对我来说 好莱坞意味着死亡
Excuse me？
你说什么？
I'm a homicide detective，remember？
我是一个谋杀警长 记得吗？
And when you see what I see，day in and day out，
当你见到所见到的这一切 一天又一天的
the violence that people do to each other，
人们互相之间血腥攻击
you get haunted.
你简直就是在受折磨
I think you know about that.
我想你该知道
What do you mean？
你什么意思？
I know what it's like to see ghosts that don't go away.
我知道阴魂不散是什么感觉
To be watching a scary movie in your head，whether you want to or not.
在大脑里上演一部恐怖片 不管你愿不愿意
Watching it alone.
就只有你独自一人观看
Ghosts are tough。You can't shoot ghosts.
鬼魂是很棘手的 你无法对鬼开枪
Can't arrest ghosts.
也逮捕不了它们
But the best way to stop being haunted is to be with people.
但是摆脱这种折磨最好的办法就是和别人在一起
You're here，you're not hiding。You've done the right thing，Miss Prescott.
你在这儿 你没有躲藏 你做的没错 普莱斯柯特小姐
What did you know about your mother？
关于你妈妈你知道些什么？
I always thought I had the perfect mom.
我总以为自己有一个完美的妈妈
Perfect family.
完美的家庭
Till I found out I was wrong。She，um…
知道我发现自己错了 她 嗯…
She had a secret life，and I tried to understand that，and，um，
她一生很神秘 我试着解开谜团 但是 嗯
soon as I thought that I had，more secrets.
很快我发现 谜团竟然越解越多
I don't know who my mom was.
我根本不知道自己的妈妈是个怎样的人
You know who she was to you.
你知道她对你来说意味着什么
Here's the deal.
这样吧
I'm off to search the set。I think what you saw is real.
我现在要去搜查片场我认为你看到的是真的
That's the good news.
那是个好消息
How is that good news？
怎么就是好消息呢？
Because that means we're dealing with an ordinary fleshandblood killer.
因为那意味着我们面对的只是一位普通的冷血杀手
I know how to handle guys like that。Oh，yeah？How？
我知道怎么对付这种人 哦 是吗？怎么对付？
Catch him… or kill him.
抓住他… 或者杀了他
Hey，Detective.
嘿 警长
What's your favorite scary movie？
你最喜欢的恐怖片是什么？
My life.
我的一生
Mine too.
我也是
We have to think。Strategize.
我们得制订个战略
Milton's the key to everything。He's a pervert，he's not a killer.
米尔顿是所有事的关键 他是个变态 但不是个杀手
He's gotta be involved somehow。We should follow him.
他肯定和这件事有牵连 我们该跟着他
We're gonna go back to the precinct and tell Kincaid and Sidney what we found out.
我们现在要去警局告诉金凯德和西德妮我们发现了什么
My Gale would be much more aggressive.
我饰演的盖尔会更加咄咄逼人
My Gale would suspect everybody.
我饰演的盖尔会怀疑任何人
My Gale would… Shut up！
我饰演的盖尔会… 闭嘴！
Riley here。Dewey，it's Sidney.
我是莱利 请讲 杜威 是我 西德妮
Hey，Sid。I'm with Gale。We're on our way to see you.
嘿 西德妮 我和盖尔在一起 我们正赶去找你
No.
不用了
Listen，I'm not at the station.
听着 我并不在警局
John Milton called me and said he had something to tell me.
约翰米·尔顿打电话给我说有事情要告诉我
Something about my mom。I'm going to meet him at his house.
关于我妈妈的事 我现在去他家见他
Wait，Sid，I'm not so sure that's a good idea.
等等 西德妮 我不认为这是个好主意
It's okay。Kincaid's with me。I've got official bigtime…
没关系的 金凯德和我一起去 我有官方的…
L.A.P.D。protection，but I'd feel better if you were there.
洛杉矶警察保护 但是如果你们也能来我会更加安心
We're on our way，but still，Sid… Thanks.
我们马上到 但是 西德妮… 谢谢
What？
什么？
Looks like we're going to that party after all.
看来我们最后还是得去那个聚会
Hey，guys。Come on in。Join the party.
嘿 伙计们 来啊尽情享受吧
Yeah，well，actually，we're here to see Sidney.
好吧 但事实上 我们是来找西德妮的
Really？Sidney's here。Where？
是吗？西德妮在这 哪？
Where's Sidney？She's right there！
西德妮在哪？就在那儿！
Jesus！Not 「Sidney，」Sidney.
老天！不是扮演的西德妮 是真的西德妮
Like I'm 「Gale」 and she's Gale.
就像我是扮演盖尔而她才是盖尔
Sidney Prescott？Yeah.
西德妮·普莱斯柯特？是的
No，I'd never invite her here。She's on her way.
不 我没请过她 她说她来了啊
Well，the more the merrier.
好吧 人越多越好
God，this house is incredible.
天啊这房子真让人震惊
It's old Hollywood.
这是老好莱坞
Yeah，could the dude have more money？
是的 这家伙还会有更多的钱吗？
Supposedly，Milton has a secret screening room…
恐怕米尔顿还有间秘密放映室…
that was like the scene back in the '70s，you know.
就像70年代的那种感觉 你们应该知道
It was，like，drinks and drugs，and girls，and movies and shit.
就好像有酒 毒品 姑娘 电影还有那事儿
Wow！Wish I could've seen it.
哇哦！真希望我能看看
Big old screening room shouldn't be too hard to find。I'm gonna go check this place out.
仿古的大型放映室应该不难找 我去找找看
Whoa！Just one damn minute。There's a psycho killer on the loose.
哇哦！等等 有个变态杀手可是一直在伺机而动
And you want to go traipsing around this gigantic mansion？
而你想一个人在这个大屋里晃荡？
Have you ever actually seen the Stab movies？
你有没有看过杀戮系列的电影？
Every time this dude enters a room，he ends up a goddamn shish kebab.
每次那家伙进入房间 就代表着最后会有人死去
I'll go with you，Roman。There you go。You guys wanna come？
我和你一起去 罗曼 好的 你们要去吗？
It'll be okay。We're gonna stick together.
这样很好 我们可以待在一起
You're not stickin'。Wait up。We're gonna stay here and wait for Sid.
你们这可不叫待在一起 等等 我们在这里等西德妮
We'll be right back！
我们马上回来！
If，if you were a screening room，
如果 如果你是个放映室
where would you be？
你会在哪儿呢？
I bet in the basement.
我打赌在地下室
I don't like basements.
我不喜欢地下室
Ooh，it's spooky.
哦 令人毛骨悚然
Ooh，Weredad。Damn，it's dark in here.
哦 亡父的海报 该死 这儿太黑了
I loved that movie.
我喜欢那部电影
Forget the movie！What if Milton's crazy，
别提什么电影了！如果米尔顿疯了
and he's gonna Jump outta his screening room with a sling blade or something？
那他会不会手持风扇叶片突然出现在放映室？
He won't。You sure about that？
他不会 你确定？
What's down there？Zombies and aliens.
谁在那儿？野人和外星人
You know，what you look like without makeup，Jennifer.
知道吗 就像没化妆的你 珍妮弗
Stop pretending I wasn't the best you've ever had.
别装作我不是你最好的女友
Stop pretending I even remember.
别以为我还对你念念不忘
Stop pretending！
别装了！
Roman？
罗曼？
Any sign of her？No.
有她的迹象吗？没有
This is so strange.
真是太奇怪了
It sure is.
是的
Do you have caller I.D。on your cell phone？Yeah.
你手机有来电显示吗？有
Use it and press 「send.」
打回去看看
What the hell？
什么声音？
What is this thing？
这是什么？
Is this what he…
这不是那个杀手的…
Hell…
该死…
Dewey，he's got our voices.
杜威 他录制了我们的声音
He's got Sid's.
他也录制了西德妮的声音
He's got us all.
他搞到了我们所有人的声音
Oh，my God。We gotta find her。Come on.
哦 天啊我们得找到她 来
All right，take the gun.
好的 拿上枪
Go find Roman and Jennifer。I'm gonna get the others.
你去找罗曼和珍妮弗 我去找另两个
Be careful。You too.
小心 你也是
Tyson！Angelina！You up there？
泰森！安吉丽娜！你在在那儿吗？
Roman！
罗曼！
Tyson！
泰森！
Angelina！
安吉丽娜！
Damn it！
该死！
Aah！Okay，come on。We gotta get out of here.
啊！没事 来 我们得离开这儿
Where's Angelina？I don't know.
安吉丽娜在哪儿？我不知道
She went in here，I came in after her，now she's gone.
她去了里面，我原本跟着她的，现在找不到她了
Great.
太好了
What's wrong？Looks like Stab 3 is back in production.
出什么事了？恐怕杀戮3要重新上演了
Roman！
罗曼！
Jennifer！
珍妮弗！
Roman！
罗曼！
Jennifer！
珍妮弗！
Roman？
罗曼？
Is he dead？Yeah，very.
他死了？是的 必死无疑
Dewey！Dewey！
杜威！杜威！
Dewey？
杜威？
Dewey！
杜威！
God，I'm sorry。Look，I found a secret passage.
天啊抱歉 看呐 我发现一条秘密通道
Roman's dead.
罗曼死了
What？What？The killer's here。Come on.
什么？什么？　 那个杀手在这里 来
Let go of me！I'm getting out of here！You're not safe alone！
让我走！我要出去！你一个人不安全！
Listen to me！
听我说！
I did not fuck that pig Milton
我才不会为了一个角色
to get a leading role just to die here
和那个垃圾米尔顿干那事儿
with secondrate celebrities like you two！
像你们俩一样死在这个二流聚会上
Gale！I'm up here。Come on.
盖尔！我在上面 来
Dewey！You guys should get out too.
杜威！你们也该离开
It's crazy to still be here.
再待在这里简直是疯了
Come on！
快！
Dewey！
杜威！
Gale，Jennifer，up here。Dewey，here.
盖尔 珍妮弗 我在这儿 杜威 找到你了
He got Roman and Angelina too.
他杀了罗曼和安吉丽娜
We'll be safer if we stick together，won't we？
我们在一起就能安全 不是吗？
Of course。Why…
当然 为什么…
What's goin' on？Oh，shit！
出什么事了？哦 该死！
Hey！Dewey！
嘿！杜威！
Dewey！
杜威！
No！
不！
Police！Help！Help！
警察！救命啊！救命啊！
Police！Help！
警察！救命啊！
Oh，you motherfucker！
哦 你个狗娘养的！
Damn！
该死！
Dewey！Dewey！
杜威！杜威！
Behind the mirror，Dewey！
我在镜子后面 杜威！
Gale！Get away！Dewey！
盖尔！走开！杜威！
Do you hear something？Get away from me，you asshole。You don't scare me.
你听到什么了吗？离我远点 垃圾 我不怕你
Look，Gale。The mirror's moving.
看呐 盖尔 镜子在动
Gale！Gale！Stand back，Gale.
盖尔！盖尔！退后 盖尔
You can't kill me。I'm the killer in Stab 3。I'm the killer！
你不能杀我 我是杀戮3里面的杀手 我是杀手！
Gale，cover！
盖尔 遮住耳朵！
Dewey！
杜威！
Tyson！
泰森！
Tyson！I'm gonna check down here。You call for help.
泰森！我下去看看 你们打电话求救
Okay.
好的
Tyson！
泰森！
Tyson？Any sign of him？
泰森？有他的踪迹吗？
No。All right。I'm gonna check out front.
没有 好的 我去前面看看
Dew…
杜…
Gale！
盖尔！
Dewey？
杜威？
Gale！
盖尔！
Who is this？Dewey，it's me.
是谁？杜威 是我
Gale… where are you？
盖尔… 你在哪儿？
I'm in the basement。I'm trapped。Where？
我在地下室 被困住了 哪儿？
There's a door in the kitchen.
厨房里有个门
Hurry.
快
Wait。How do I know this is you，Gale，and not the killer？
等等 我怎么知道你是盖尔本人 而不是杀手？
Dewey，open the fucking door。It's me.
杜威 快帮我从外面把该死的门打开 就是我
Well，don't you think that's what the killer would say？
嗯 你不认为杀手就是会这样说吗？
Come on。He's out cold… at the bottom of the stairs.
拜托 他昏过去了… 就在楼梯下面
Hey！
嘿！
Dewey。Dewey.
杜威 杜威
All right，all right。It's pizza，not a party.
好了 好了 只是个批萨 可不是舞会
Everybody get back to work。Anybody seen my fucking partner？
所有人回去工作 有人见过我那垃圾搭档吗？
Hey，Morgan，what did you say？
嘿 摩根 你说什么？
Hello？Hello？
你好？你好？
Who is this？Who is this？
哪位？你是哪位？
Um，who's calling？Um，who's calling？
嗯 谁打来的？嗯 谁打来的？
Gale，Dewey，whoever，call me back.
盖尔 杜威 不管谁 稍后再打给我
I can only hear myself.
我现在只能听到自己的声音
I only hear you too，Sidney.
我也只听到你的声音 西德妮
Who is this？The question isn't who I am.
是谁？问题不是我是谁
The question is：Who's with me？
而是：我抓了谁？
Sidney，stay away！Sidney！
西德妮 别过来！西德妮！
Don't do it。If you do one thing to attract attention to yourself，
不要冲动 如果你作出任何异常的举动
one thing，I'll kill them both.
任何一个举动 我就会杀了他们
Now，do you have somewhere we can be alone？
现在 你能去个安静的地方和我单独谈谈吗？
Yes。Yeah。Go there.
好 好 去吧
Oh，it's hard being friends with you，Sidney.
哦 和你成为朋友真的很困难 西德妮
When you're friends with Sidney，you die.
当你成为西德妮的朋友的时候 你就会死
Well，these friends don't have to，Sidney。It's up to you.
好吧 这几个朋友可以不必死 这全看你了
How do I know their voices are… Are real？
我怎么知道这声音是… 是真的？
How do you know you're not hearing things？
你怎么知道听到的可能是录音？
How do you know I'm not someone in your head？
你怎么知道我是不是那个萦绕在你脑海的那个人？
Somewhere you know.
有些事你知道的
Don't come here，Sidney！Dewey！
别过来 西德妮！杜威！
Or do you？You're dead.
你来不来？你死定了
I don't want them。I want you.
我不想杀他们 我只想杀你
It's simple。You show yourself，they survive.
事情很简单 你现身 他们能活下去
You run，they die.
你跑了 他们就死定了
Oh，God！
哦 天啊！
Don't you wanna know，Sidney，who killed her？
西德妮 你想不想知道谁杀了她？
Don't you wanna know who killed your mother？
你想不想知道谁杀了你妈妈？
Seen Kincaid？Yeah，I saw him go out.
见到过金凯德吗？是的 我看着他出去的
Where？
地点？
She'd have been so happy，Sidney，to know we'd be together.
知道我们能在一起 西德妮 你妈妈会很开心的
Where？I'll call you when you're on your way.
地点？你出去我自然会告诉你
Shit。Shit.
该死 该死
Shit.
该死
Holy shit.
What？You follow directions well，Sidney.
怎么样？你做得很好 西德妮
Now，welcome to the final act.
现在 欢迎来到最后的舞台
See that metal detector？Use it.
看到那个金属探测仪了？探测自己
All over，Sidney。Everywhere.
全身都要扫描 西德妮 全身上下
Everywhere。The other leg too.
每一处都要扫描 另一只腿也要扫描
Show it to me.
拿出来
Throw it in the pool.
扔进泳池
Now，come inside，Sidney.
现在 进来 西德妮
No fucking way。How do I know they're not dead already？
想都别想 我怎么知道他们还活着？
They're right inside，waiting for you.
他们就在里面 等着你
Look for yourself.
你自己看看
Now that we're all here，the party can begin.
既然我们都到了 舞会现在开始
Dewey。Sid.
杜威 西德妮
Where is he？I don't know.
他在哪？不知道
He's right there！
他在那儿！
Oh，shit.
哦 该死
Think again.
动脑子想想吧
It's your turn to scream，asshole.
现在轮到你尖叫了 垃圾
Yeah！
太好了！
It's okay。Just give me a second.
没事了 等一会儿
Okay。Hurry，Sid.
好的 快点 西德妮
Sidney？
西德妮？
Where is he？
他去哪儿了？
Be careful！
小心！
I heard shots。Tyson's dead。What's goin' on？
我听到枪声 泰森死了 出什么事了？
What're you doin' here，Kincaid？Lookin'for you.
你在这儿干嘛 金凯德？找你啊
Tyson said there was a party here tonight，and I thought，「Uhoh.
泰森说这儿今晚有个舞会 那我就想 「啊哦
Third act celebration.「 Thought I better check it out.
最后的狂欢「 我想我还是过来看看比较好
Alone？Where's your partner？
就你一个人？你的搭档呢？
Hey，Miss Prescott.
嘿 普莱斯柯特小姐
I'm here to help。Put the gun down.
我是来帮忙的 把枪放下
Put the gun down.
把枪放下
No！
不！
Sid！Wake up，Sid！Sid，come on！
西德妮！醒醒 西德妮！西德妮 醒醒！
Wake up！Sidney！
醒醒！西德妮！
Shoot him，Sid。Sidney.
开枪 西德妮 西德妮
Sid。Shoot the fucker！
西德妮 朝那个混蛋开枪！
Shoot him！
开枪！
You want me，motherfucker？Come and get me.
你不是想杀我吗 畜生？来抓我吧
Run！
快跑！
Sid.
西德妮
Come in here… please.
进来吧… 求求你
It's Just me，Sid.
是我 西德妮
Oh，I was so pretty.
哦 我是如此美丽
Everybody loved me.
每个人都喜欢我
Have you missed me，Sidney？
你有想我吗 西德妮？
Would you like to hold me one last time？
你想不想最后拥抱我一次呢？
What's the matter？What are you staring at？
怎么了？你在看什么？
Don't you remember your… Mother？
你不记得自己的… 妈妈了？
You're not going anywhere，Sidney.
你哪都逃不了了 西德妮
It's time you came to terms with me and with Mother.
你是时候和我还有你妈妈达成协议了
Maybe you never knew her at all，Sidney.
也许你从来都不了解她 西德妮
Maybe you Just can't get past the surface of things.
也许你无法看穿表象
Who the hell are you？The other half of you.
你到底是谁？你的另一半
I searched for a mother too，an actress named Rina Reynolds.
我也在找我妈妈 一个名叫瑞娜·雷诺兹的女演员
Tried to find her my whole life.
试着去了解她的一生
And four years ago，I actually tracked her down.
四年前 我总算找到她了
Knocked at her door，thinking she'd welcome me with open arms，
敲开她的门 原以为她会张开双臂欢迎我
but she had a new life
但是他有了一个新的生活
and a new name：Maureen Prescott.
和新的名字：莫琳·普莱斯柯特
You were the only child she claimed，Sidney.
你是她唯一承认的孩子　西德妮
She shut me out in the cold forever.
她永远把我甩在了冰天雪地之中
Her own son.
她的亲生儿子
Roman Bridger，director。And brother.
罗曼·布雷吉 导演 你哥哥
She slammed the door in my face.
她当着我的面重重的关上了门
She said I was Rina's child，and Rina was dead.
她说我是瑞娜的孩子 而瑞娜已经死了
And it struck me.
这深深地触动了我
What a good idea！So I watched her.
这是多好的主意！所以我开始监视她
I made a little home movie.
我拍了一部小制作的家庭电影
A little family film.
一部小制作的家庭电影
It seems Maureen… Mom…
看起来莫琳… 妈妈…
She really got around。I mean，Cotton was one thing.
她开始走红了 我是说 卡顿那是另一回事
Everybody knew about that.
所有人都知道
But Billy's father？That was the key.
但是比利的爸爸？那是关键
Your boyfriend didn't like seeing his daddy in my film too much.
你男朋友不想看到他爸爸在我的电影里太入戏
He didn't like it at all.
他非常不喜欢
But once I supplied the motivation，
但是我给了他们一点动机
all the kid needed was a few pointers.
那些孩子需要的只是一些指导
Have a partner to sell out in case you get caught，find someone to frame.
找个合作伙伴 万一自己被抓了还能来个栽赃嫁祸
It was like he was making a movie.
就好像是他在拍这部电影
You。This is all because of you.
你 都是因为你
I'm a director，Sid.
我是导演 西德妮
I direct。Oh.
我要导演这一切 哦
I had no idea… they were gonna make a film of their own.
我别无选择… 他们拍了一部自己的电影
What a film it turned out to be，huh？
电影最后会变成什么样 啊？
I mean，introducing Sidney，the victim.
我的意思是 介绍西德妮 受害人
Sidney，the survivor。Sidney，the star！
西德妮 那个幸存者 西德妮 那个明星！
Oh。All right。You're gonna be all right。Just apply pressure.
哦 好了 你会没事的 顶住
Here，take this。Get the son of a bitch.
这儿 拿着这个 杀了那个畜生
Let's go.
走
Fine，you got what you wanted，hero and villain facetoface.
很好 你得到了你想要的 英雄和恶棍面对面交流
You know what happens now？The villain dies！
你知道现在是什么情况吗？坏人必死！
Exactly！But，
是的！但是
I'm not the villain，Sid，you are.
我不是坏人 西德妮 你才是
Here he is，the man who gave away your mother's innocence.
他在这儿 这个男人毁了你妈妈的清白
Huh？What he did to her made her a slut.
嗯？就是他让你妈妈变成一个荡妇
Didn't it？Huh？
不是吗？嗯？
She never recovered from that night，right here in this room.
她一直没有从那晚在这个房间中发生的惨剧中恢复过来
They fucked her three ways from Sunday。Ruined her life.
他们从周日开始用各种办法玩弄她 毁了她的一生
Ruined yours too，didn't it，Sid？
也毁了你的一生 不是吗 西德妮？
You hate him，Sid？
你恨他吗 西德妮？
Come on，I know you do。I'm sure you do.
来吧 我知道你恨他 我很肯定你恨他
I know who you are.
我知道你骨子里是什么样的人
I know what happened to my mother，and understand，
我知道我妈妈发生了什么事 我也明白
I'm gonna make you pay！
我会让你付出代价的！
That's what the police are gonna find on Milton's answering machine…
这是警察会在米尔顿的答录机听到的东西…
right next to his lifeless，mutilated corpse.
就放在他奄奄一息 血肉模糊的尸体边上
What？Can't hear ya.
什么？听不清你说什么
You don't have to do this。Just tell me what you want.
你没必要这么做 告诉我你想要什么
I can make it happen。Any picture.
我都可以答应 任何图片
Name your budget。Script approval.
或是你的预算 还是你写的剧本
Final cut！I already have it.
还有最后的剪辑！我已经有了
No！
不！
God！You spineless bastard！
天啊！你个没种的混蛋！
No，Sid，that would be you。You did it all.
不 西德妮 是你 是你干的
You did it，you called them all.
都是你干的 你打电话叫他们来
Even your closest… friends.
甚至是你最亲密的… 朋友
Living in total isolation，the pressure of another movie about you，
一直与世隔绝 这是另一部电影给你带来的压迫
the discovery that Milton destroyed Mommy dearest，
发现米尔顿毁了你妈妈的一生
you finally just snapped！
你终于愤怒了！
One，two，three！
一 二 三！
And who's our hero，huh？The sole survivor.
那谁是我们英雄 啊？唯一的幸存者
Who's the one who bravely faced down the psychopath and
谁是勇敢面对变态杀手并且
killed her with her own knife？
以其人之道还治其人之身的英雄？
You're gonna pay for the life you stole from me，Sid.
你要为偷了我的一生而付出代价 西德妮
For the mother，and for the family，and for the stardom and…
偷了我的妈妈 偷了我的家庭 还有那些演员和
Goddamn it！Everything you have that should've been mine！
该死！你所拥有的一切都是我的！
Why don't you stop your whining and get on with it？
你为什么不停止抱怨做自己该做的事情？
I've heard this shit before！
这些屁话我早就听过了！
Stop！
住嘴！
You know why you kill people，Roman？Do you？
你知道你为什么要杀人吗 罗曼？你知道吗？
I don't wanna hear it！
我不想听到！
'Cause you choose to！There is no one else to blame！
因为是你自己选的！你不能怨恨任何你！
Stop！Fucking damn it！
住嘴！该死的东西！
Why don't you take some fucking responsibility？
你怎么就没种负起责任？
Fuck you！Fuck you！
靠你妈的！靠你妈的！
Sid？Sidney？
西德妮？西德妮？
Sidney？
西德妮？
Sidney！
西德妮！
Leave her alone！
不要伤害她！
Dewey，do something！
杜威 快想想办法！
Stand back！Dewey！
退后！杜威！
Sid！
西德妮！
Sid.
西德妮
Sid？
西德妮？
Where is he？
他在哪儿？
Hey.
嘿
Lose something？Found something.
找不到什么东西吗？找到某些东西
There's gotta be another way in there！Come on！
肯定还有别的路！来！
You hurt her，I swear I'll kill you！
你敢伤害她 我发誓我会杀了你
Dewey！
杜威！
Down this way。There's another hallway.
下来这边 有个走廊
There's another door down here.
下面另有个门
This thing's not budging.
这些东西没用
Look around for something heavy。Go that way。Okay！
找些重家伙 去那边 好的！
I shot you.
我明明打中你了
I guess we think alike.
我想我们的想法一样
Mother's dead.
妈妈的死
And there is nothing you can do about that.
你对这件事无能为力
I still got to make my movie.
我还是要继续我的电影
Stab 3，right？
杀戮3 对吗？
Kincaid，hang in there.
金凯德 坚持住
Roman？
罗曼？
It was Roman？
罗曼是凶手？
Be careful，Sid。Randy said the killer's always superhuman.
小心点 西德妮 兰迪说凶手一般都是超人
Yeah，well，he wasn't superhuman，Dewey.
是的 但是 他可不是什么超人 杜威
He wasn't superhuman at all.
他根本不是超人
You can't fuckin' kill me！Head！
你们根本杀不死我！头部！
Head！Head，Dewey！What？
头部！头部杜威！什么？
Head！Shoot him in the head.
头部！射他的头部
Thanks.
谢谢
No problem.
没关系
Oh.
哦
Look.
看呐
Come on，Cherokee。Come on.
过来 切罗基 过来
Yeah，she's doin'great。Yeah.
是的 她做的很不错 是的
Look.
看
What are you doing with that？
你拿着这个干嘛呢？
Um，will you sign it for me，Gale？
嗯 你愿意给我签个名吗 盖尔？
You hate that book.
你讨厌这本书
Besides，I'm done with that kind of reporting.
而且 我也不再做那种报道了
For me。Will you sign it for me？
为了我 你愿意为我签个名吗？
You're a nut.
你真是固执
Mmm。Okay.
嗯 好吧
Will you？Dewey.
你愿意吗？杜威
I know it'll never work，and you know it'll never work.
我知道这招没什么用 你也知道
But，what I'm asking is… just to see if we're wrong.
但是 我想的是… 我们是否错过了什么
We don't know everything，Gale.
我们不可能知道所有的事 盖尔
I mean，you think you do，but…
我的意思是 你认为你知道 但是…
You're a brave man，Dewey Riley.
你是个勇敢的男人 杜威·莱利
I'm really scared right now.
我现在真的很害怕
Inside.
进去
Sid，we've been waiting for you。We're gonna start a movie.
西德妮 我们等你很久了 我们要开拍一部电影
What kind of movie？You have to come and see.
什么电影？你一定要来看看